(function(e){function t(t){for(var n,a,r=t[0],h=t[1],l=t[2],d=0,u=[];d<r.length;d++)a=r[d],Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(s,a)&&s[a]&&u.push(s[a][0]),s[a]=0;for(n in h)Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(h,n)&&(e[n]=h[n]);w&&w(t);while(u.length)u.shift()();return i.push.apply(i,l||[]),o()}function o(){for(var e,t=0;t<i.length;t++){for(var o=i[t],n=!0,a=1;a<o.length;a++){var r=o[a];0!==s[r]&&(n=!1)}n&&(i.splice(t--,1),e=h(h.s=o[0]))}return e}var n={},a={app:0},s={app:0},i=[];function r(e){return h.p+"js/"+({about:"about",english:"english"}[e]||e)+"."+{about:"45cec9be",english:"0004156f"}[e]+".js"}function h(t){if(n[t])return n[t].exports;var o=n[t]={i:t,l:!1,exports:{}};return e[t].call(o.exports,o,o.exports,h),o.l=!0,o.exports}h.e=function(e){var t=[],o={about:1,english:1};a[e]?t.push(a[e]):0!==a[e]&&o[e]&&t.push(a[e]=new Promise(function(t,o){for(var n="css/"+({about:"about",english:"english"}[e]||e)+"."+{about:"b3ba9c72",english:"e08334a0"}[e]+".css",s=h.p+n,i=document.getElementsByTagName("link"),r=0;r<i.length;r++){var l=i[r],d=l.getAttribute("data-href")||l.getAttribute("href");if("stylesheet"===l.rel&&(d===n||d===s))return t()}var u=document.getElementsByTagName("style");for(r=0;r<u.length;r++){l=u[r],d=l.getAttribute("data-href");if(d===n||d===s)return t()}var w=document.createElement("link");w.rel="stylesheet",w.type="text/css",w.onload=t,w.onerror=function(t){var n=t&&t.target&&t.target.src||s,i=new Error("Loading CSS chunk "+e+" failed.\n("+n+")");i.code="CSS_CHUNK_LOAD_FAILED",i.request=n,delete a[e],w.parentNode.removeChild(w),o(i)},w.href=s;var m=document.getElementsByTagName("head")[0];m.appendChild(w)}).then(function(){a[e]=0}));var n=s[e];if(0!==n)if(n)t.push(n[2]);else{var i=new Promise(function(t,o){n=s[e]=[t,o]});t.push(n[2]=i);var l,d=document.createElement("script");d.charset="utf-8",d.timeout=120,h.nc&&d.setAttribute("nonce",h.nc),d.src=r(e);var u=new Error;l=function(t){d.onerror=d.onload=null,clearTimeout(w);var o=s[e];if(0!==o){if(o){var n=t&&("load"===t.type?"missing":t.type),a=t&&t.target&&t.target.src;u.message="Loading chunk "+e+" failed.\n("+n+": "+a+")",u.name="ChunkLoadError",u.type=n,u.request=a,o[1](u)}s[e]=void 0}};var w=setTimeout(function(){l({type:"timeout",target:d})},12e4);d.onerror=d.onload=l,document.head.appendChild(d)}return Promise.all(t)},h.m=e,h.c=n,h.d=function(e,t,o){h.o(e,t)||Object.defineProperty(e,t,{enumerable:!0,get:o})},h.r=function(e){"undefined"!==typeof Symbol&&Symbol.toStringTag&&Object.defineProperty(e,Symbol.toStringTag,{value:"Module"}),Object.defineProperty(e,"__esModule",{value:!0})},h.t=function(e,t){if(1&t&&(e=h(e)),8&t)return e;if(4&t&&"object"===typeof e&&e&&e.__esModule)return e;var o=Object.create(null);if(h.r(o),Object.defineProperty(o,"default",{enumerable:!0,value:e}),2&t&&"string"!=typeof e)for(var n in e)h.d(o,n,function(t){return e[t]}.bind(null,n));return o},h.n=function(e){var t=e&&e.__esModule?function(){return e["default"]}:function(){return e};return h.d(t,"a",t),t},h.o=function(e,t){return Object.prototype.hasOwnProperty.call(e,t)},h.p="/examination/dist/",h.oe=function(e){throw console.error(e),e};var l=window["webpackJsonp"]=window["webpackJsonp"]||[],d=l.push.bind(l);l.push=t,l=l.slice();for(var u=0;u<l.length;u++)t(l[u]);var w=d;i.push([0,"chunk-vendors"]),o()})({0:function(e,t,o){e.exports=o("56d7")},"309d":function(e,t,o){"use strict";t["a"]=[{text:'Peter wondered why he didn\'t have many friends. The reason was he was always taking, never giving. \n  One day Peter told Bill, "I\'d like to give a party on Saturday, I\'d like you to come and bring Martha, too.""Thanks, Peter. We\'d be happy to come.""Perhaps you\'d like to bring your violin. You and Martha sing well together. I\'m sure everyone will want you to sing for us."That was how Peter began to plan his party. Next he asked another friend, Betty, to bring a cake."You make the best cake in the world, Betty, and I like to eat your cake better than have one from the bakery."Peter invited a few other friends to come to his party. He didn\'t forget to ask something from each one of them. He even asked Jim and Mary Jackson to let him give the party at their house! They agreed. \n  The party was a big success. However, as the guests were leaving, they said"Thank you "to Bill and Martha for the music, Betty for the cake, the Jacksons for the use of the house and to others for their hard work. To Peter they just said,"Thanks for the invitation."',questions:[{question:"The party was held at Peter's friend's house.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The Jacksons did hard work for the party.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"All his friends liked Peter. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Peter tried his best to give the party.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"From the story, we can see Peter was a selfish man.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:"How men first learnt to invent words is unknown; in other words, the origin of language is a mystery. All we really know is that men, unlike animals, somehow invented certain sounds to express thought and feelings, actions and things, so that they could communicate with each other; and that later they agreed upon certain signs, called letters, which could be combined to present those sounds, and which could be written down. Those sounds, whether spoken or written in letters, we call words.\n  The power of words, then, lies in their associations - the things they bring up before our minds. Words become filled with meaning for us by experience; and the longer we live, the more certain words recall to us the glad and sad events of our past; and the more we read and learn, the more the number of words that mean something increases.\n  Great writers are those who not only have great thoughts but also express these thoughts in words which appeal powerfully to our minds and emotions. This charming and telling use of words is what we call literary style. Above all, the real poet is a master of words. He can convey his meaning in words which sing like music and which by their position and association can move men to tears. We should therefore learn to choose our words carefully and use them accurately, or they will make our speech silly and vulgar.  ",questions:[{question:"The origin of language is _________.",options:["a legend handed down from the past ","a matter that is hidden or secret","a question difficult to answer","a problem not yet solved"],answer:"D"},{question:"What is true about words? ",options:["They are used to express feelings only.","They can not be written down.","They are simply sounds.","They are mysterious."],answer:"C"},{question:"The real power of words consists in their ______.",options:["properties","characteristics ","peculiarity","representative function"],answer:"D"},{question:'By "association" in the last paragraph, the author means ______.',options:["a special quality","a joining of ideas in the mind","an appearance which is puzzling","a strange feature"],answer:"B"},{question:"Which of the following statements about the real poet is NOT true? ",options:["He is no more than a master of words.","He can convey his ideas in words which sing like music.","He can move men to tears.","His style is always charming."],answer:"A"}]},{text:"When you take a walk in many of the cities in the West, you often see a lot of people walking dogs. It is still true that a dog is the most useful and faithful animal in the world. But the reasons why people keep a dog have changed.\n  In the old days, people used to train dogs to protect themselves against attacks by other beasts. And later, they came to realize that the dog was not only useful for protection but willing to obey his master. For example, when people used dogs for hunting, the dogs would not eat what was caught without permission. But now, people in the city need not protect themselves against attacks of an animal.\n  Why do they keep dogs, then? Some people keep dogs to protect themselves from robbery, but the most important reason is for companionship. For a child, a dog is his best friend when he has no friends to play with. For young couples, a dog is their child when they have no children. For old couples, a dog is also their child when their real children have grown up. So the main reason why people keep dogs has changed from protection to friendship.",questions:[{question:"It is true that a dog is the most important animal in the world.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"According to the passage, dogs were trained for protection against other animals in the past.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Dogs were used for hunting because they always obeyed their masters. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The most important reason for people in the city to keep dogs now for companionship.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The main idea of the passage is that the dog is a useful and friendly animal.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:'This story is about a young man. He worked very hard at his lessons. He was too busy to have a rest. At last, he couldn\'t go to sleep. Every night, when he went to bed, he closed his eyes and tried to sleep. But the more he tried, the more he stayed awake. \n  After a while he decided to visit the doctor. "I just can\'t go to sleep at night. What should I do?" "I have a suggestion," said the doctor. "Try counting numbers. By the time you reach one thousand, you\'ll be asleep. I am sure of it." \n  The next day the man reached the doctor\'s office. "Well," said the doctor, "how are you today? Did you try my suggestion?" \n  The man still looked tired. "Yes," he said, "I tried counting one, two, three...up to one thousand. But when I reached five hundred and sixty-nine, I began to feel sleepy. I had to get up and drink some tea so that I could go on counting up to one thousand, but then I still couldn\'t fall asleep." ',questions:[{question:"The young man couldn’t go to sleep because he had worked too hard and became ill.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The doctor asked the young man to count numbers while he was lying in bed.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The young man returned to the doctor’s office the next day because he wanted to thank the doctor. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The young man counted from 1 to 569 and got up to drink some tea. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The young man in fact was not able to count numbers. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"}]},{text:'Mr Tom Forester lived by himself a long way from town. He hardly ever left his home, but one day he went into town to buy some things in the market. After he had bought them, he went into a restaurant and sat down at a table by himself. When he looked around, he saw several old people put glasses on before reading their newspapers, so after lunch he decided to go to a shop to buy himself some glasses too. He walked along the road, and soon found a shop.\n  The man in the shop made him try on a lot of glasses, but Tom always said, "No, I can\'t read with these."\n  The man became more and more puzzled(迷惑不解), until finally he said, "Excuse me, but can you read at all?"\n  "No, of course I can\'t!" Tom said angrily. "If I was already able to read, do you think I would have come here to buy glasses?" ',questions:[{question:"Mr Forester lived alone in a city.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Tom almost never went into town.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The old people in the restaurant read their newspapers with glasses off.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The shop Tom went into sold glasses for people who could not see well.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"What kind of mistake did Tom make? He left his money in the restaurant. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"}]},{text:"What is the best way to learn a language? We should remember that we learned our own language well when we were children. If we could learn a second language in the same way, it would not seem so difficult. Think of what a small child does. He listens to what people say and tries to imitate what he hears. When he wants something he has to ask for it. He is using the language, talking in it, thinking in it all the time. If people had to use a second language all the time, they would learn it quickly. \n  We learn our own language by hearing people speak it, not by seeing what they write. We imitate what we hear. In school, though you learn to read and write as well as to hear and speak, it is best to learn all the new words through the ear. You can read them, spell them and write them later. ",questions:[{question:"Everyone learns his mother language when he is a child. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"A small child learns to speak by imitating what people say. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"People can learn a language quickly if they imitate it. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"It is best to learn new words through reading first. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The best way to learn a language is to use the language all the time.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:'He has done what Mohammed Ali did for boxing, Michael Jordan for basketball, Roger Federer for tennis and Tiger Woods for golf. Twenty-three-year-old Michael Phelps has become a phenomenon in swimming. \n  At the 2008 Summer Olympic Games, he won eight gold medals. That was more than the whole Australian team could put together. He beat Mark Spitz\'s 1972 record of seven wins in the pool at the one Games. Phelps has put his name next to seven world records.\n  Nine days, 17 games, morning and night he competed and won. He had to beat former world record-holders and gold medalists. He had to turn their wins into old news.\n  "I\'m just lucky to have the drive that I have, the talent that I have and the excitement for the sport," Phelps said after winning his last medal. \n  After the Olympics, swimming will not be in the news so much. But Phelps has decided to keep working to popularize it.\n  "I don\'t want this sport to be an every-four-years sport," Phelps said. "Over the past four years, it\'s skyrocketed. I\'m honored to help this sport for the next generation of swimmers who will have it better than I have."',questions:[{question:"Phelps is a swimmer.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Roger Federer is famous for tennis.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:'"竞争"is closest in meaning to the underlined word "phenomenon".',options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Phelps wants to change swimming to an every-four-years sport.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:'"Swimming is going to be popular" can be the most suitable title for this article.',options:["T","F"],answer:"B"}]},{text:"A couple of months ago, I went to a department store to buy a few things for the house. I needed a set of curtains for the living room, two table lamps, a rug and several cushions. I asked them to deliver the things as soon as possible, but they said that they were unable to send them out until 20 days later. After about 3 weeks, I received only the curtains and table lamps. I was a little disappointed when I didn't receive all the items I had bought. But nevertheless, I was eager to see what the curtains and lamps looked like. I first opened the package with the curtains. I had bought a lovely light blue, and instead they had sent me a horrible dark purple. Well, you can just imagine how angry I was. Then I opened the boxes with the lamps. They were exactly what I'd ordered. But one of the lamp shapes was damaged. The next I did was to telephone them to complain. They promised to come and pick them up immediately and also to replace them with the correct order. It has been two weeks since my complaint. They have neither picked up the wrong items nor sent me the rest of my order.",questions:[{question:"The woman want the store to deliver the items was in a couple of weeks.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The woman was pleased when she saw the items they had delivered.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Her complaint was ignored in the end.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"After three weeks, the woman received only the curtains and table lamps.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Besides curtains, table lamps, the woman bought a cushion.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"}]},{text:"Modern life is impossible without traveling. The fastest way of traveling is by plane. With a modern airliner you can travel in one day to places which it takes a month or more to get to a hundred years ago. \n  Traveling by train is slower than by plane, but it has its advantages. You can see the country when you are traveling through. Modern trains have comfortable seats and dining-cars. They make even the longest journey enjoyable. \n  Some people prefer to travel by sea when possible. There are large liners and river boats. You can visit many other countries and different parts of your country on them. Ships are not so fast as trains or planes, but traveling by sea is a very pleasant way to spend a holiday.\n  Many people like to travel by car. You can make your own timetable. You can travel three or four hundred miles or only fifty or one hundred miles a day, just as you like. You can stop wherever you wish - where there is something interesting to see, at a good restaurant where you can enjoy a good meat, or at a hotel to spend the night. That is why traveling by car is popular for pleasure trips, while people usually take a train or plane when they are traveling on business.\n  ",questions:[{question:"From the passage, we know the fastest way of traveling is by plane.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:'The underlined word "They" in the passage refers to comfortable seats and dining-cars.',options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"If we travel by car, we can make our own timetable.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"When people travel on business, they usually take a plane or a car.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Four ways of traveling are mentioned in the passage.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:'Here is a story told an American general (将军) who was a very important figure in the American army during the First World War. Everybody in the United States knew him and many people wished to have a picture or something of his in their homes.\n  Soon after the war the general returned to Washington. One day he went to a dentist and had six teeth pulled out. A week later the general heard that his teeth were being sold in curiosity shops (古玩店) at $5 each. On each of the teeth there was a label with the name of the general and words, "Buy these teeth and show them to your friends at home." The general got angry. He rushed to his office and ordered six officers to go around the city and buy all his teeth.\n  The officers went out and visited every curiosity shop in the capital. They were away from the office all day. In the evening they returned and put on the table in front of the general the teeth they had bought. They had collected 175 teeth.',questions:[{question:"The general's teeth were sold in the museum.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"In the evening, the officers went back with all the teeth which cost $175.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The general felt angry when he heard his teeth were sold.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"There was the general's picture on the label of each tooth. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The general ordered his men to look for his teeth and buy all of them.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:"On a practical level, teachers need a wide variety of skills and abilities. They have to be ready to spend many hours at home planning their lessons and preparing homework. They have to be well organized in class, patient with students, able to appear bright and interested even if they are in fact tired or unhappy, and lively enough to control a group of young people for almost 200 days a year. Outside the classroom, they may have to prepare teaching materials, to choose books to use as texts, to help organize the work of other teachers, or to organize spare time activities for students. \n  If you think that you have all the necessary qualities, you may feel that you would like to be a teacher. If you live in the United States, one way to decide is by joining a club for future teachers, such as Student Action for Education. Clubs like this give advice about your field, and also allow you to watch teachers at work, attend meetings and experiment with teaching methods and equipment. You could also talk with the job advisor at your school or university. Finally, you could try teaching a younger student or becoming an advisor at a summer camp for children. Any activity in which you are dealing with, children will help you decide whether you have a calling for teaching.  ",questions:[{question:"A teacher should show a firm mind that is able to control tiredness and unhappiness.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The first paragraph is mainly about how to plan lessons and prepare homework.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The second paragraph is about ways to decide whether teaching should be one's future employment.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Student Action for Education is an activity at a summer camp.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The author suggests that talking with job advisors will help you make decisions on taking a teaching job.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:"Today the official language of the United Sates and most of Canada is English. However, French almost became the official language because of a war.\n  The French and Indian War was fought between 1754 and 1763. The name of this war is not accurate because the war was actually between England and France. The Indian fought on the side of the French.\n  France and England were trying to gain control of North America. France held Canada, and England held part of what is now the United States. However, France tried to expand its land by moving southward into New York, Pennsylvania, Ohio, and Virginia. When the French built a fort on the Ohio River, the residents in Virginia sent George Washington to attack the fort in 1754. However, the French defeated Washington.\n  The French, aided by Indians, outsmarted(更精明) the English and won many early battles. Later, the British began to do well against the French. In the final battle in Quebec, Canada, General Wolfe of England faced General Montcalm from France. Both general died in this battle, but the English outlasted(比...持久)the French and won the battle. Thus, most of North America today has the English culture and language.",questions:[{question:"A good title for this selection is The French and Indian War.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Most of North America today has the English culture and language.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"General Wolfe died in France.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Washington lost his battle at the fort on the Ohio River at the end of the war.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Both general died in the final battle.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:'Six people were travelling in a compartment(包厢) on a train. Five of them were quiet and well behaved, but the sixth was a rude young man who was causing a lot of trouble to the other passengers.\n  At a station this young man got out with his two heavy bags. None of the other passengers helped him, but one of them waited until the rude young man was very far away. Then he opened the window and shouted to the young man, "You left something behind in the compartment!" Then he closed the windows again.\n  The young man turned around and hurried back with his two bags. He was very tired when he arrived, but he shouted through the window, "What did I leave behind?"\n  As the train began to move again, the passenger who had called him back opened the window and said, "A very bad impression!"',questions:[{question:"One of the passengers helped the young man.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The sixth young man was impolite.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Having heard the shout, the young man was frightened.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The young man left something unpleasant in the train.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The other passengers were not happy with the young man's behavior.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:"The sun is the closest star to earth. It takes 8 minutes for the light from the sun to reach our earth. The distance from the sun to earth is one astronomical unit(天文单位). It is about 150 million kilometers.\n  Energy from the sun heats the earth's surface. The earth would be too cold for life without our star's heat energy. Other stars are too far away to give the earth enough heat energy for life. Scientists wonder if there is life near other stars.\n  Our sun is an average(平均的) size star. It appears like the largest one, because it is the closest star. Some stars are smaller than our sun. Very small stars are called dwarf(短小的)stars. Some of them are no larger than our small planets. Some stars are much larger than our sun. The largest stars are called giant(巨大的)stars. \n  Not all stars are the same distance from the earth. The different distances make some giant stars appear very small. Astronomers (天文学家)use light-year to talk about distance in space. A light-year is the distance the light travels in one year. The star, Alpha Centauri is the closest star besides our sun. It is over 4 light-year away from earth. It takes light from this star over four years to reach the earth.",questions:[{question:"The sun is a star while the earth is a star.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Our sun is a small size star.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The sun looks like the largest star because it is the closest star.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Very small star are called dwarf stars and very large stars are called giant stars.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Astronomers use meter to talk about distance in space.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"}]},{text:"If you've been joining in chat room conversations, or trading e-mail with net pals, you have become one of the millions who write in a special, short form of English.\n  Throughout the world, every night children and their elders are \"talking\" online ─ many of them are talking at the same time.\n  It's fast: trying talking to six people once. It's convenient: three or four words per exchange. It takes cleverness, concentration and quick fingers.\n  And it requires very simple language. There's neither time nor space for explanations. Why waste precious time telling six friends you have to leave for a moment to take care of your little brother when BRB (=be right back) will do?\n  Want to enter a conversation? Just type PMFJI (=pardon me for jumping in).\n  Interested in whom you're talking to? Type A/S/L, the common request to know your pal's age, sex and location. You may get 15/M/NY as a reply from your pal. \n  If something makes you laugh, say you're OTF (=on the floor), or LOL (=laughing out loud), or join the two into ROTFL (=rolling on the floor laughing).\n  And when it's time to get back to work or go to bed, you type GTG (=got to go) or TTYL (=talk to you later).\n  People want to write as fast as possible, and they want to get their ideas across as quickly as they can. Capital letters are left in the dust, except when expressing feeling, as it takes more time to hold down the \"shift\" key and use capitals. Punctuation is going too.",questions:[{question:"When people are online, they talk by using body language.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The Internet makes many people in the world talking at the same time.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:'The sentence "There\'s neither time nor space for explanations" means that people online have to express themselves in a simple way.',options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"If you get 19/M/HK as an answer to your A/S/L, it means you are talking to 19 boys from Hong Kong at the same time.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"People seldom use capital letters or punctuation marks in order to save online time.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:'My friend\'s grandfather came to America from Eastern Europe. After being processed (移民入境检查) at Ellis Island, he went into a cafeteria in Lower Manhattan to get something to eat. He sat down at a table and waited for someone to take his order. But nobody came to him. Later a woman with a plate full of food sat down opposite him and told him how a cafeteria worked.\n  "Start out at the end," she said. "Just go along the line and pick out what you want. At the other end he\'ll tell you how much you have to pay."\n  "I soon learned that\'s how everything works in America," the grandfather told my friend. "Life is like a cafeteria here. You can get anything you want only if you are willing to pay the money. You can even get success, but you\'ll never get it if you wait for someone to bring it to you. You have to get up and get it yourself."',questions:[{question:"From the passage, we know if you want to get success in America, you should try to get it by yourself.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The old man came from Eastern Europe.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The old woman sat down opposite the old man so that she could serve him.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:'The word "it" in the third paragraph refers to the success one wants to get.',options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:'The best title for the passage is "How to Eat in a Cafeteria".',options:["T","F"],answer:"B"}]},{text:'Tibet is among the most popular places for Chinese tourists. The number of travelers to Tibet has grown by 10% every year for a few years. Since July 1, 2006, when the first train ran 1956 kilometers from Xining to Lhasa, more and more people have been to Tibet.\n  The train stops at several famous places along the way, such as Qinghai Lake, Kunlun Mountain, and the Potala Palace. Passengers can also enjoy many activities during the journey, like Tibetan dancing and Karaoke.\n  On the train, passengers can have tea, eggs and noodles for breakfast, and fried chicken and green vegetables for lunch and dinner. Unlike most Chinese trains which have open-hole toilets, this one has special toilets which can collect the waste. There is also a special rubbish system in the train that keeps the environment clean. All the windows on the train can protect people from the bright sunlight. TV and electrical sockets for computers and mobile phones are available on the train.\n  Because there isn\'t much oxygen there, trains will have oxygen masks for those who need them. It makes passengers feel more comfortable when they have enough oxygen on the famous "roof of the world". There are also doctors on the train to make sure that all of the travelers are safe. ',questions:[{question:"Karaoke is not a place of interest.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Unlike most Chinese trains, the train has special windows.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:'The underlined word "them" in the last paragraph refers to oxygen masks.',options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"We can learn from the passage that doctors are available on the train to help.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:'The best title of the passage is "Beautiful Views in Tibet".',options:["T","F"],answer:"B"}]},{text:'Tom arrived at the bus station quite early for Paris bus. The bus for Paris would not leave until five to twelve. He saw a lot of people waiting in the station. Some were standing in line, others were walking around. There was a group of schoolgirls. Their teacher was trying to keep them in line. Tom looked around, but there was no place for him to sit. \n  He walked into the station cafe. He looked up at the clock there. It was only twenty to twelve. He found a seat and sat down before a large mirror on the wall. Just then, Mike, one of Tom\'s workmates came in and sat with Tom.\n  "What time is your bus?" asked Mike. "There\'s plenty of time yet" answered Tom. \n  "Well, I\'ll get you some more tea then" said Mike.\n  They talked while drinking. Then Tom looked at the clock again. "Oh! It\'s going backward" he cried. "A few minutes ago it was twenty to twelve, and now it\'s half past eleven."\n  "You\'re looking at the clock in the mirror." said Mike. Tom was so sad. The next bus was not to leave for another hour. Since then Tom has never liked mirrors.',questions:[{question:"Tom went into the station cafe because Mike asked him to have a cup of tea.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Tom and Mike talked while drinking.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"When Tom looked at the clock in the mirror, it's actually half past twelve.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"From the story we know that when we look at a clock in a mirror, we will find it's going backward.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Tom arrived in Paris on time.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"}]},{text:"Computers can injure you. Most other injuries happen suddenly. For example, if you fall off a bike and break your arms, it happens very quickly. But computer injuries happen slowly. \n  You probably know how to ride a bike safely. Now learn to use a computer safely. \n  Your eyes \n  Too much light can injure your eyes, so never sit too close to a computer screen. Your eyes should be at least 50cm from the screen. Remember to look away from it sometimes. This gives your eyes a rest. \n  When you use a computer, the window should be on your left or your right. If it is behind you, the light will reflect on (反射) the screen. If the window is in front of you, the sun and the screen will both shine into your eyes. \n  Your hands and wrists \n  Hand and wrist injuries can happen because the hands and wrists are moved in the same way hundreds of times. If you use a keyboard for a long time, follow these three rules:1) Rest your wrists on some thing. 2) Keep your elbows (肘) at the same height as the keyboard. 3) Stop sometimes and exercise your hands, wrists and fingers in a different way. \n  Your back \n  Some people sit for many hours in front of a computer. If you sit in the wrong way, you can injure your back or your neck. So you should sit with your back straight. The top part of the screen should be in front of your eyes. Your forearms, wrists, hands and the upper part of your legs should all be parallel (平行) to the floor. If you are sitting for a long time, get up every 30 minutes and exercise your arms, legs and neck. \n  Enjoy your computer, but use it safely. ",questions:[{question:"A computer screen may injure your eyes if your eyes are too close to it.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Hand and wrist injuries are caused when you get plenty of exercise.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Your eyes and hands will be safe if you often take rests from working.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"It is good for your back and neck if you sit in the right way.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:'The best title for the text is "How to Protect Your Eyes."',options:["T","F"],answer:"B"}]},{text:"When John and Victoria Falls arrived in New York City for one-year stay, they did not bring very many things with them. They had planned either to live in a furnished apartment or to buy used furniture. But they soon learned about a new system that more and more people are using. The renting of home furnishings (bed, tables, dishes, and so on) has become one of America's fastest growing businesses.\n  What kinds of people rent their home furnishings instead of buying them? People who are international business or government officials, foreign students, airline workers, young married couples - people whose job or business may force them to move frequently from one city to another. They save a lot of trouble and the cost of moving their furniture each time. They simply rent new furniture when they reach their new homes. Young people with little money do not want to buy cheap furniture that they may soon dislike. They prefer to wait until they have enough money to buy furniture they really like. Meanwhile, they find they can rent better quality furniture than they could afford to buy.\n  One family, who now have a large, beautiful home of their own, liked their rented furniture so much that they decided to keep renting it instead of buying new things. But usually people don't like to tell others about it. The idea of renting home furnishings is still quite new, and they are not sure what their neighbors might think. ",questions:[{question:"Which of the following has become one of America’s fastest growing businesses? ",options:["Selling home furnishings.","Renting furnished apartments.","Selling used furniture.","Renting home furnishings."],answer:"D"},{question:"Why do some people prefer to rent furniture?",options:["Because the furniture they get in this way is new.","Because it saves them a lot of money.","Because it saves them much trouble and money.","Because they can always get better quality furniture in this way."],answer:"C"},{question:"What can you infer from the passage?",options:["The idea of renting furniture is not acceptable.","Renting furniture is not popular in the couple’s home town.","Only those who don’t have enough money to rent furniture.","People usually grow to like the furniture they have rented."],answer:"B"},{question:"Which of the following can best serve as the title of the passage?",options:["Rent or Buy?","A New Way of Getting Home Furnishings.","Furnished Apartments.","A New Idea."],answer:"B"},{question:"Young people liked renting home furniture because_________.",options:["they have less money","they don’t want to buy old furniture","the new furniture is of good quality","they don’t have much money and don’t want to buy the cheap furniture"],answer:"D"}]},{text:'Elvis Aron Presley, often called "the king of rock music", died on August 16th, 1977, at the age of forty-two. He left a great influence on popular music, and millions of fans. During his lifetime, Elvis sold more than four hundred million records. After Presley died, many of his records rose quickly. When Presley died, many mourners journeyed to Memphis, Tennessee, Presley\'s home, to pay their last respects. While most of these fans knew a lot about the songs of Elvis, few of them knew the story of how Elvis had his first record which was for his mother. He paid four dollars to a small Memphis recording shop, and recorded two songs. The songs were "My Happiness" and "That\'s Where Your Heartaches Begin". Sam Philips, who owned the shop where Elvis made the record, liked Presley\'s songs. He said he would call him some day. About a year later, Philips did call and asked him to cut a record. This first record had "Blue Moon of Kentucky"on one side, and "That\'s All Right, Mama"on the other. ',questions:[{question:"The passage is mainly about how Elvis Presley began his career.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Mourners are usually record-producers.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Without the record for his mother, Elvis might not have become a star.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"When Presley died, people went to Memphis for his mother's story of life.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The passage shows that many people loved Elvis's songs.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:"Lovely dog aged 5\n  I'm moving and can't take him with me .Very good with children. I'd like to give it away to a good home.\n  Tel:8631966\t\n             Wanted\n       Welcome to HiLo's Store\n  Take any ole pair of shoes to us between now and 30 Sep.And you will pay not more than ten dollars for any new pair of shoes.Your old shoes will be given to the poor people.\n  A women's dress size 12 silk $ 150\n  Also three dresses for girls between 5and 9 years old,$120 the three.\n  More information call Laura at 5998326.\t",questions:[{question:"If Mrs Evans is interested in the dresses, she may call 5998326.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"You needn't pay if you want to get a lovely dog.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"If Mrs Evans wants to buy all the dresses, she has to pay ＄270.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"If you give an old pair of shoes to HiLo's Store, you can get any new pair of shoes with only 10 dollars.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The old shoes will be given to beggars.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"}]},{text:"Mr. Simpson worked in a shop which sold, cleaned and repaired hearing-aids(助听器). One day an old gentleman entered and put one down in front of him without saying a word. \n  \"What's the matter with it?\" Mr. Simpson said. The man didn't answer. Of course Mr. Simpson thought the old man must be deaf and that his hearing-aid must be faulty, so he said again, more loudly, \"What's wrong with your hearing-aid, sir?\" Again the man said nothing. So Mr. Simpson shouted his question again as loudly as he could. \n  The man then took a pen and a piece of paper and wrote: \"It is not necessary to shout when you are speaking with me. My ears are as good as yours. The hearing-aid is my wife's, not mine. I've just had a throat(咽喉) operation, and my problem is not that I can't hear, but that I can't speak.\"",questions:[{question:"The old gentleman went to Mr. Simpson's shop to buy a hearing-aid.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"When the old didn't answer him, Mr. Simpson thought the old man was very strange. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The old gentleman's wife's hearing-aid was faulty.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The old man finally made himself understood by writing on a piece of paper.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The old man could not answer Mr. Simpson because he had just had a throat operation. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:"Can trees talk? Yes, but not in words. Scientists have reason to believe that trees do communicate with each other. Not long ago, researchers learned some surprising things. First a willow tree attacked in the woods by caterpillars (毛虫) changed the chemistry of its leaves and made them taste so terrible that they got tired of the leaves and stopped eating them. Then even more astonishing, the tree sent out a special smell--a signal causing its neighbors to change the chemistry of their own leaves and make them less tasty.\n  Communication, of course, doesn't need to be in words. We can talk to each other by smiling, raising our shoulders and moving our hands. We know that birds and animals use a whole vocabulary of songs, sounds, and movements. Bees dance their signals, flying in certain patterns that tell other bees where to find nectar (花蜜) for honey. So why shouldn't trees have ways of sending message?",questions:[{question:"It's implied that caterpillars do not feed on leaves that have an unpleasant taste.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The willow tree described in the passage protects itself by growing more branches.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The willow tree was able to communicate with other trees by giving off a special smell.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"It can be inferred from the passage that bees communicate by making special movements.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The author holds that the incident described in the passage must be checked more thoroughly.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"}]},{text:"After having lived for over twenty years in the same district, Albert Hall was forced to move to a new neighborhood. He surprised his landlord by telling him that he was leaving because he could not afford to buy any more chocolate.\n  It all began a year ago when Albert returned home one evening and found a large dog in front of his gate. He was very fond of animals and as he happened to have a small piece of chocolate in his pocket, he gave it to the dog. The next day, the dog was there again. It held up its paws and received another piece of chocolate as a reward. Albert called his new friend \"Bingo\". He never found out the dog's real name, nor who his owner was. However, Bingo appeared regularly every afternoon and it was quite clear that he preferred chocolate to bones. He soon grew dissatisfied with small pieces of chocolate and demanded a large bar a day. If at any time Albert neglected his duty, Bingo got very angry and refused to let him open the gate. Albert was now at Bingo's mercy and had to bribe him to get into his own house! He spent such a large part of his weekly wages to keep Bingo supplied with that in the end he had to move somewhere else. ",questions:[{question:"Albert lived there for many years.                 ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Albert was moving because he did not like the place.                   ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Albert and the dog became friends a year ago.           ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The dog visited Albert every day because it wanted the chocolate.     ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:'Albert "had to bribe him" means he had to take care of him.             ',options:["T","F"],answer:"B"}]},{text:'Clowns(小丑) like to make people laugh. They paint their faces and put on funny noses. Sometimes they put on a sad face but most of the time they put on a happy face. They also wear funny clothes.\n  Most clowns work in circuses. They do all kinds of silly things to make the audience laugh. They run, jump, fall down, turn somersaults (翻滚,斤头), and roll over. They ride donkeys backwards. They push each other in wagons or wheelbarrows(独轮车). Sometimes they shout and sing. Clowns are funny men, and occasionally, women, too! A circus is not a circus without clowns!\n  Children especially enjoy watching clowns. A clown named Cookie often visits hospitals to entertain sick children as well as older people. Sick people need to laugh. It helps them to get better faster.\n  There is an old saying: "Laughter is good medicine." ',questions:[{question:"Clowns make people laugh by doing all kinds of silly things.                         ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Clowns are mostly female.                                  ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:'The sentence "A circus is not a circus without clowns" means a circus will not be of much fun if it has no clowns.',options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Clowns are a great favorite with children.                      ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:'The best interpretation of the old saying "Laughter is good medicine" may be laughter cures people\'s diseases.                                                 ',options:["T","F"],answer:"B"}]},{text:"In earlier days few people read Whitman's poems. One person who did read them was Abraham Lincoln who was then a country lawyer. He liked the strength and honesty of Whitman's words. He often read them to visitors in his office. Whitman didn't know Lincoln, but he wrote a long article about slavery. Whitman was against slavery. He wanted to see a new kind of president, not a professional politician, but an ordinary working man. This man would be wise, healthy and middle-aged. He would have a beard. Whitman didn't know it, but he was describing Lincoln. Before he was a lawyer, Lincoln worked with his hands. He was wise, healthy and middle-aged, and he had a beard.\n  In 1860 Abraham was elected the president of the United States. In March 1865, Whitman was in Washington. Abraham Lincoln became president for the second time. Whitman watched the ceremony. The two men had never met but they had seen each other. Washington was very hot in summer. Sometimes Lincoln went outside the city. He passed Whitman's house on the way. He and Whitman often nodded to each other.\n  Early in April the civil war ended. But on April 13 someone shot President Lincoln, and on 14 Lincoln died. To Whitman it was like the death of a friend. He loved Lincoln so much. He wrote a poem to express his feelings about the death of the president. It was one of his saddest and most beautiful poems.",questions:[{question:"Whitman wrote a long article about slavery because he was strongly against slavery.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"A working man was not the kind of president that Whitman wanted to see.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Lincoln was the right person because he was a worker with his hands.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Lincoln died before the civil war ended.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Whitman wrote a poem to support his friend Lincoln.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"}]},{text:"When I was a little girl, my brothers and I collected stamps for many years. My mother didn't use to work during the week, but she worked in the post office near our house on Saturdays, and she used to bring home all the new stamps as soon as they were issued (发行).\n  On the day of the World Cup football final in London in 1966, we were very excited because England were playing West Germany in the final. When we were having lunch, my mother told us to go to the post office straightaway after the match if England won, but she didn't tell us why. At 2 o'clock my mother went back to work as usual, while the rest of the family were watching the football on TV at home. Although she wasn't watching the match, she was listening to it on the radio. \n  England won 4:2 and so my brothers and I ran to the post office. As we burst in, my mother was standing behind the counter. She was waiting to sell us a very special limited edition with ENGLAND WINNERS on each stamp. We were over the moon.\n  We still have it todaym, and perhaps it is worth a lot of money.  ",questions:[{question:"This passage mainly tells us ______.",options:["the author and her brother used to like stamps very much","the author had a very kind mother","the author and her brothers had an unforgettable experience in collecting stamps","their mother used to support them by working in the post office"],answer:"C"},{question:"According to the passage, her mother worked in the post office ______.",options:["during the week","on Saturdays","on Sundays","for six days"],answer:"B"},{question:"Their mother told them to go to the post office straightaway after the match if England won, but she didn't tell them why. Why do you think she did that? ",options:["She wanted to give them a surprise.","She doubted if she would get the stamps.","She forgot to do that.","She thought it unnecessary to tell them the reason."],answer:"A"},{question:'What does the sentence "We were over the moon." mean?  ',options:["We jumped high.","We were extremely happy about it.","We watched the moon for a long time.","We couldn't sleep the whole night."],answer:"B"},{question:"What is the best title for this passage? ",options:["My Childhood","My Mother","A Precious Stamp","A Memorable Experience in Collecting Stamps"],answer:"D"}]},{text:"Peter liked music very much when he was at school, but when he went to the university, he decided to study medicine instead. After he passed the examinations and became a doctor, he had to work in a hospital for some time. There he discovered that a lot of patients were happier and less worried about their illnesses if they could hear pleasant music. When Peter became a surgeon and began to work for himself, he decided to keep his patients happy by having a tape recorder in his waiting room, playing beautiful music for them.\n  But soon after the tape recorder was put in the waiting room, Peter's nurse heard a woman who was sitting in the crowded waiting room one morning complain, \"Here we're all waiting to see the doctor, and he's just playing the piano in his office instead of doing his work!\"",questions:[{question:"Peter liked music when he was at school.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Peter had to pass some examinations after he became a doctor.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Peter decided to play music for his patients because he couldn't leave music.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Peter put a recorder in his waiting room.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The woman complained because she thought Peter wasn't working.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:"In England, people often talk about the weather because they can experience four seasons in one day. In the morning the weather is warm just like in spring. An hour later black clouds come and then it rains hard. The weather gets a little cold. In the late afternoon the sky will be sunny, the sun will begin to shine, and it will be summer at this time of a day.\n  In England, people can also have summer in winter, or have winter in summer. So in winter they can swim sometimes, and in summer sometimes they should take warm clothes. \n  When you go to England, you will see that some English people usually take an umbrella or a raincoat with them in the sunny morning, but you should not laugh at them.\n  If you don't take an umbrella or a raincoat, you will regret later in the day.",questions:[{question:"People in England often talk about the weather, because the sky is sunny all day.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"From the story we know that when black clouds come, there is a heavy rain.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:'The sentence "People can also have summer in winter." means "it is sometimes too warm in winter."',options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"In the sunny morning some English people usually take a raincoat or an umbrella with them because their friends ask them to do so.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The best title for this passage is Summer or Winter in England.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"}]},{text:"Until a few years ago, vans were commercial vehicles used mostly by business firms as delivery trucks. Today, the van has become a palace on wheels. It is a place where the owner of a van, called vanner, can relax, visit with good friends, eat, drink, sleep and even watch television.\n  A van may often look like an art museum on wheels. The exterior of vans is a visual feast of colors and styles. Many vans have paintings of various kinds on the sides. Each van is decorated and finished to reflect the personality of its owner. The most luxurious(豪华的)van has TV, a refrigerator and a sink, etc. Some even have paintings on the walls.\n  Van is very popular with young married couples with small children, and with young people, such as high school and university students. The latter frequently use their vans for traveling parties, often going from place to place, or city to city, gathering friends along the way.\n  In 1966 there were about 190,000 vans registered in US. By 1976 sales of vans were more than 2 million a year. What is the reason for van boom(快速发展)? Freedom and chance to be with other people are some of most often expressed reasons.",questions:[{question:"Vans were used as delivery trucks before.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The Rapid Increase of Vans is the main topic of the passage.\t\t\t\t\t\t",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"A van often looks like an art museum on wheals.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"People with small children aren't vans lovers.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Vans are booming, because vanners need freedom.\t\t",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:"Very few people were coming to eat at the White Rose Restaurant, and its owner didn't know what to do. The food in his restaurant was cheap and good, but nobody seemed to want to eat there.\n  Then he did something that changed all that, and in a few weeks his restaurant was always full of men and their lady friends. Whenever a gentleman came with a lady, a smiling waiter gave each of them a beautiful menu. The menus looked exactly the same on the outside, but there was an important difference inside. The menu that the waiter handed to the man gave the correct price for each dish and each bottle of wine; while the menu that he handed to the lady gave a much higher price! So when the man calmly ordered dish after dish and wine after wine, the lady thought he was much more generous than he really was! ",questions:[{question:"The waiter gave a beautiful menu to the guests when a gentleman and his lady friend came into the restaurant.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The menus for the guests were the same on the outside but different inside.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The male guest could remain calm when he ordered dish after dish because he was rich.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The lady thought of her friend very generous after a meal at this restaurant.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The story mainly suggests that people like to go to expensive restaurants.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"}]},{text:"The Antarctic(南极洲) is actually a desert. It is the only continent on the earth without a river or a lake.\n  The Antarctic is all ice all year round. The warmest temperature ever recorded there is zero, at the South Pole. Explorers used to think that a place so cold would have a heavy snowfall. But less than ten inches of snow falls each year. That is less than half an inch of water. Ten times that much moisture falls in parts of the Sahara.\n  The little snow that falls in Antarctic never melts. It continues to pile up deeper and deeper year after year. When the snow gets to be about eighty feet deep it is turned to ice by the weight of the snow above it.",questions:[{question:"Antarctica is called a desert because it has little moisture and no lakes or rivers.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The Antarctic has ten times as much moisture as the Sahara.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The temperature in the Antarctic is always above zero.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The snow in Antarctic is very deep because it piles up year after year.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The snow turns to ice when the snow above it is heavy enough .",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:"Time spent in bookshop can be most enjoyable, whether you are a book-lover or only there to buy a book as a present. You may even have entered the shop just to find shelter from a sudden shower. Whatever the person, you can soon become totally unaware of your surroundings. The desire to pick up a book with an attractive design is irresistible, although this method of selection ought not be followed, as you might end up with a rather uninteresting book. You soon become lost in some books or other, and usually it is only much later that you realize you have spent far too much time there and must hurry to keep some forgotten appointment --- without buying a book, of course.\n  The opportunity to escape the realities of everyday life is, I think, the main attraction of a bookshop. There are not many places where it is possible to do this. A music shop is very like a bookshop. You can go to such places as much as you wish. If it is a good shop, no assistant will approach you with the greeting: \"Can I help you, sir?\" You needn't buy anything you don't want. In a bookshop, an assistant should remain in the background until you have finished reading. You may want to find out where a particular section is. Then, and only then, are his services necessary. But when he has led you there, the assistant should leave politely and look as if he is not interested in selling a single book.",questions:[{question:"The best title for this passage may be The Attraction of Bookshops. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"According to the author, the best way to escape the realities of everyday life is to chat with assistants in a bookshop. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"In a good bookshop, you are satisfied. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"An assistant in a bookshop helps you on your entering the shop. ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"According to the passage, people go to bookshops only to buy books.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"}]},{text:'When weather is hot, you go to a lake or an ocean. When you are near a lake or an ocean, you feel cool. Why? The sun makes the earth hot, but it cannot make the weather very hot. Although the air over the earth becomes hot, the air over the water stays cool. The hot air over the earth rises.\n  Then the cool air over the water moves in and takes the place of the hot air. When you are near a lake or an ocean, you feel the cool air when it moves in. You feel the wind, and the wind makes you feel cool.\n  Of course, scientists cannot answer all of our questions. If we ask, "Why is the ocean full of salt?" scientists will say that the salt comes from rocks. When a rock gets very hot or very cold, it cracks. Rain falls into the cracks. The rain then carries the salt into the earth and into the rivers. The rivers carry the salt into the ocean. But then we ask, "What happens to the salt in the ocean? The ocean does not get more salty every year." Scientists are not sure about the answer to this question.\n  We know a lot about our world. But there are still many answers that we do not have, and we are curious. ',questions:[{question:"The main idea of the passage is that people feel cool when they are near a lake or an ocean.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"You feel cool when you are near a lake or an ocean because the water is colder than the earth.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Now scientists know what happens to the salt in the ocean.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"A rock cracks when rain falls.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"People are always curious about the world around them because there are many answers that they do not have.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:"Young people have a new shape these days. They are about 20 pounds heavier than people of their age were 60 years ago. They are about four inches taller, too. These facts come from J. M. Tanner, a professor in England. \n  J. M. Tanner has been measuring people from all over the world for a long time. He has also studied people's growth records of the past 100 years. \n  \"Children today are bigger than ever before,\" he says. \"Today's nine-year-olds look like eleven-year-olds looked back in 1900.\" \n  According to Tanner, adults are also taller than ever before. \n  But the biggest change can be seen in young people. That's because boys used to keep on growing until they reached age 26. But today they stop growing at 18 or 19. Most girls stop growing even earlier. So today's teenagers are bigger than 26-year-olds were 60 years ago. \n  What is causing this change? Professor Tanner says it's proper food. Good food alone cannot make you grow beyond your natural limits. Your final height is partly caused by the height of your parents and grandparents. But eating proper food can help you reach your final height, and reach it early in life. \n  Will people keep on getting bigger? Will we have a race of giants? No - at least not if the US is an example. Tanner says that we have eaten proper food for years, and our growth rate has already begun to level off. ",questions:[{question:"This article talks mainly about the change of teenagers' shape.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"A nine-year-old child today is older than a child of the same age a century ago.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"About 60 years ago, boys stopped growing at 26.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"According to Professor Tanner, natural limits have caused the change in height difference between young people now and those of 60 years ago.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:'The word "giants" in the text probably means short people.',options:["T","F"],answer:"B"}]},{text:"In ancient time the most important examinations were spoken, not written. In the schools of ancient Greece and Rome, testing usually consisted of saying poetry aloud or giving speeches.\n  In the European universities of the Middle Ages, students who were working for advanced degrees had to discuss questions in their field of study with people who had made a special study of the subject. This custom exists today as part of the process of testing candidates for the doctor's degree.\n  Generally, however, modern examinations are written. The written examination, where all students are tested on the same questions, was probably not known until the nineteenth century. Perhaps it came into existence with the great increase in population and the development of modern industry. A room full of candidates for a state examination, timed exactly by electric clocks and carefully watched over by managers, resembles a group of workers at an automobile factory. Certainly, during examinations teachers and students are expected to act like machines.",questions:[{question:"In the Middle Ages students never wrote exams.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The main idea of paragraph 3 is that workers now take examinations.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:'The word "degree" in paragraph 2 means academic title.',options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Modern examinations must have developed before the Middle Ages.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"It may be concluded that testing has changed since the Middle Ages.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:'A man was telling one of his friends why he was content with his married life. "My wife makes all the small decisions," he explained, "and I make all the big ones, so we never try to have too much influence in each other\'s business and never get annoyed with each other. We have no complaints and no arguments." \n  "That sounds reasonable," answered his friend sympathetically. "And what sort of decisions does your wife make?" \n  "Well," answered the man, "she decides what jobs I apply for, what sort of house we live in, what furniture we have, where we go for our holidays, and things like that." \n  His friend was surprised. "Oh?" he said. "And what do you consider important decisions then?" \n  "Well," answered the man, "I decide who should be President, whether we should increase our help to poor countries, what we should do about the atom bomb, and things like that." ',questions:[{question:"The man was content with his married life because he and his wife loved each other deeply.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"His friend didn't believe what the man said at first.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The man can decide where to work.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"We can tell from the story that the man's wife has the final say in the family.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Your choice of the title would be A Happy Married Life.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:'Li Qiu is a boy of fifteen and studying in Grade Three at Oak school. His family lives outside the town. His parents have a farm and grow a lot of vegetables on it and they often sell them in the town. These years they\'ve built a new building and bought a tractor, a motorbike, a color television, a fridge and other things. \n  Two years ago, Li Qiu began to study in a middle school. He does well in all his lessons and now he\'s becoming more and more interested in science. He likes to try out new ideas and hopes to be an inventor. This term he\'s learned electricity (电学). He always watches TV carefully. Last Saturday, when he came back home, his parents were working in the fields. He looked at the new color TV for a while. Then he began to take apart (拆) it. Three hours later his mother came in and saw him fixing the TV set. She was surprised and asked, "What are you doing here, Li Qiu?"\n  "I took apart the TV just now."\n  "Don\'t worry about it, Mummy," said the boy "I only want to know how it works."\n  "Have you refixed it together?" asked Mum. \n  "No, Mum, " the boy said in a hurry. "Look, there are some parts left. I don\'t know where to put them."',questions:[{question:"Li Qiu's house is outside the town.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Li Qiu is in Grade Two now.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Li Qiu becomes interested in science because he wants to be an inventor.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Li Qiu thought he could refix a television.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"In fact，Li Qiu has broken their TV down.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:'Smith was a landlord. He loved money very much and never gave anything to anybody. Soon he became rich.\n  One day the weather was fine. There wasn\'t a cloud in the sky and the sun was very warm. The landlord was walking along a river with his friends, when, all of a sudden, he slipped and fell into it. He cried, "Help! Help!" One of his friends held out his hand and said, "Give me your hand and I will pull you out." The landlord\'s head went under the water and then came up again, but he did not give his hand to his friends. Then another of his friends tried but the same thing happened.\n  Just then a farmer came over and saw all this. He knew the landlord very well. He said to the others, "Let me try." He held out his hand and said to the landlord, "Take my hand and I will pull you out." Hearing this, the landlord took the farmer\'s hand, and in a minute the farmer pulled the landlord out of the water.\n  All the others got very surprised at this and asked the farmer, "Why did he give his hand to you but not to us?" The farmer said, "You don\'t know your friend very well, When you say \'give\' to him, he does nothing, but when you say \'take\' he takes."',questions:[{question:"Smith was a farmer.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Smith became very rich, because he never gave anything to anybody.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"One day Smith was walking along a lake with his friends.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:'The rich man held out his hand when he heard "Take my hand."',options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"His friends knew the rich man very well.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"}]},{text:'A farmer had once made a purchase of a fine fat sheep, hoping to offer it up to the Buddha. While he was leading it home, four thieves saw him and made up their minds to steal the sheep. They knew him to be an honest person and one who thought of no more harm in others than he had in himself. They dared not take the sheep away from him  by force, for they were too near the city. Therefore, they thought hard and got an idea: they first parted company and then came to the man as if they had come from several distinct parts.\n  The first thief came up to the farm and said, "My good old man, why are you leading this dog?"\n  At this moment the second thief, coming from another direction, cried to him, "Poor old man, where have you stolen this dog?"And immediately after these words, the third thief came up and asked the farmer,"Where are you going with this handsome greyhound?"\n  The poor farmer began to doubt whether the sheep was a sheep or not. But the fourth robber put him quite beside himself by coming near him and asking what the dog cost him.\n  The farmer began to think and got the conclusion that the four men, who came from different directions, could not all be wrong. He believed that the sheep he was leading was a dog. On realizing this, the farmer went back quickly to the market to demand his money from the person who sold him the dog, leaving the dog with the four thieves.',questions:[{question:"The farmer bought a sheep in the city.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The four thieves decided to play a trick to get the sleep because the farmer was honest and could be easily cheated by their tricks.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The farmer began to have a doubt when the third thief called his sheep a dog.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The four thieves knew about the farmer.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The farmer was cheated by the four thieves.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:'One day a bookseller(书商)let a big box of books fall on his foot. "Go to see the doctor," said his wife. "No, "he said. "I\'ll wait until the doctor comes into the shop next time. Then I\'ll ask him about my foot. If I go to see him, I\'ll have to pay him."\n  On the next day the doctor came into the shop for some books. When the bookseller was getting them ready, he told the doctor about his bad foot. The doctor looked at it.\n  "You must put that foot in hot water every night. Then you must put something on it," said the doctor.\n  He took out a piece of paper and wrote on it. "Buy this and put it on the foot before you go to bed every night," he said.\n  "Thank you," said the bookseller. "And now, sir, here are your books."\n  "How much?" said the doctor.\n  "Two pounds."\n  "Good," said the doctor. "I shall not have to pay you anything."\n  "Why?" asked the bookseller.\n  "I told you about your foot. I want two pounds for that. If people come to my house, I ask them to pay one pound for a small thing like that. But when I go to their houses, I want two pounds. And I came here, didn\'t I?"',questions:[{question:"What happened to the bookseller one day?",options:["He lost a box of books.","His foot was wounded by a box of books.","He lent the doctor a box of books.","He sold out all his books."],answer:"B"},{question:"The bookseller's wife asked him ______.",options:["to go out for some medicine","to send somebody for a doctor","to go to see the doctor","to wait for the doctor to come"],answer:"C"},{question:"The bookseller didn't take his wife's advice because ______.",options:["he was afraid of the doctor","he didn't like to take medicine","he couldn't walk by himself","he didn't want to pay the doctor"],answer:"D"},{question:"The doctor paid ______ for the books.",options:["one pound","two pounds","nothing","something"],answer:"C"},{question:"The bookseller paid ______ money for seeing the doctor in the end.",options:["more","less","the same amount of","no"],answer:"A"}]},{text:"Today Newton is a very clean place. Many years ago, however, there were millions of rats in it. They attacked the cats and dogs. Sometimes a great number of them knocked down a man or woman walking home at night. The rats were very large in size and they harmed many people.\n  The Government ordered everybody to kill rats. Most people were lazy, so they didn't kill many. The Government promised to pay some money for each dead rat. That made the people very happy. They killed thousands of rats everyday. A Government officer put all the dead rats in a big pile. Sometimes a man brought hundreds in one day.\n  After two weeks there were not many rats in the city, but people still brought many rats to the Government office. The Government officer thought that people were stealing dad rats from the pile. He ordered his men to dig a deep hole and put the rats in it. Soon there were no more rats, and the Government didn't pay any more money. ",questions:[{question:"Newton is a place which ______.",options:["used to be very clean","is no longer a city","is very clean","will be very clean"],answer:"C"},{question:"When the Government first ordered the people to kill rats, the people ______.",options:["asked for some money for each dead rat","stole dead rats from the pile","were too lazy to kill many rats","killed nearly all the rats quickly"],answer:"C"},{question:"The people killed rats ______.",options:["to get money from the Government","to help the Government make the city clean","to make the Government officer happy","to protect（保护）their cats and dogs"],answer:"A"},{question:"A deep hole was dug so that ______.",options:["the rats couldn't come out to attack people at night","people could take rats from it easily","people would kill more rats","nobody could take any rats from the pile"],answer:"D"},{question:"What is the best topic for this passage?",options:["How to Kill Rats","Newton一A City of Rats","How Newton Became a Very Clean Place","How Newton Became a Famous City"],answer:"C"}]},{text:"The fourth Thursday in November is called Thanksgiving Day. In the United States, it is an annual occasion to show thanks to God for his goodness.\n  As a historical, national and religious holiday, Thanksgiving Day began with the English in Plymouth Colony. As far back as 1621, after a long bitter winter and the gathering of the first harvest, these early settlers shared a feast with the local Indians and offered prayers of thanksgiving. The first national Thanksgiving Day was proclaimed(颁布) by President Washington on November 26, 1789. President Lincoln revived the custom in 1863.\n  It was not until 1941 that the U.S. Congress adopted a resolution(决定), setting the fourth Thursday of November as an annual Thanksgiving Day. Thus what began as a religious celebration of the harvest has since become a nationwide holiday.\n  Now Thanksgiving Day is usually a family day, celebrated with a traditional turkey dinner and a happy reunion. Schools are closed on Thanksgiving Day and the day after. Many people, including students studying in another state, often travel long distances to spend the holiday at home.",questions:[{question:"The passage is mainly about how Thanksgiving Day came into being.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Thanksgiving Day was first celebrated in 1621 by English settlers of the Plymouth Colony.  ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"President Washington set Thursday, November 26, 1789 as the First National Thanksgiving Day.  ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Since 1863, the fourth Thursday of November has been set as an annual Thanksgiving Day, a nationwide holiday.   ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The pattern of the Thanksgiving celebration has not changed through the years. The basic traditional food on Thanksgiving Day is roast turkey.  ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:"In the United States, it is not customary to telephone someone very early in the morning. If you telephone him early in the day, while he is shaving or having breakfast, the time of the call shows that the matter is very important and requires immediate attention. The same meaning is attached to telephone calls made after 11:00 pm. If someone receives a call during sleeping hours, he assumes it's a matter of life or death. The time chosen for the call communicates its importance.\n  In social life, time plays a very important part. In the U.S.A. guests tend to feel they are not highly regarded if the invitation to a dinner party is extended only three or four days before the party date. But it is not true in all countries. In other areas of the world, it may be considered foolish to make an appointment too far in advance because plans which are made for a date more than a week away tend to be forgotten. The meaning of time differs in different parts of the world. Thus, misunderstandings arise between people from different cultures that treat time differently. Promptness is valued highly in American life, for example. If people are not prompt, they may be regarded as impolite or not fully responsible. In the U.S. no one would think of keeping a business associate waiting for an hour, it would be too impolite. A person, who is 5 minutes late, will say a few words of explanation, though perhaps he will not complete the sentence.",questions:[{question:"What is the main idea of this passage? ________",options:["It is not customary to telephone someone in the morning and in sleeping hours in the U.S.","The role of time in social life over the world.","If people are late, they may be regarded as impolite or not fully responsible in the U.S.","Not every country treats the concept of time as the same."],answer:"B"},{question:"What does it mean in the passage if you call someone during his or her sleeping hours? _______",options:["A matter of work.","A matter of life or death.","You want to see him or her.","You want to make an appointment with him or her."],answer:"B"},{question:"Which of the following time is proper if you want to make an appointment with your friend in the U.S. A.?",options:["at 7:00 am","at 4:00 pm","at the midnight","at 4 am"],answer:"B"},{question:"Which of the following statements is true according to the passage? ________",options:["In the U.S.A. guests tend to feel they are highly regarded if the invitation to a dinner party is extended only three or four days before the party date.","No misunderstandings arise between people from different cultures about the concept of time.","It may be considered foolish to make an appointment well in advance in the U.S.A..","Promptness is valued highly in American life."],answer:"D"},{question:"From the passage we can safely infer that _______",options:["it’s a matter of life or death if you call someone in day time.","the meaning of time differs in different parts of the world.","it makes no difference in the U.S. whether you are early or late for a business party.","if a person is late for a date, he needn’t make some explanation."],answer:"B"}]},{text:'Bill turned the key in the heavy lock and put it calmly in his pocket. He did so from a certain kind of fear. This was the only entrance to the house. Though Tom would be away for at least three days, Bill had a strange feeling of his nearness. In the stillness he seemed to hear Tom\'s voice. He turned round quickly, but there was only the girl.\n  The girl carrying an oil lamp led Bill upstairs. She stopped and raised the lamp in each doorway, staring at him meanwhile. Satisfied he was the only guest, Bill came to the last door.\n  "You sleep here, sir," she said, giving him the lamp. "Your friend slept here, too."\n  "Good night, miss," he said politely.\n  Her lips moved in reply, but he didn\'t catch the words. Her eyes never for a moment left his face. He stepped in, and as he turned to close the door she was still standing there. In the silence he felt a little terrified now.\n  He shut the door in the girl\'s face then, leaving her in the dark. He opened it again almost at once. She had disappeared without a sound. A deep mistrust suddenly came to him. Why had that girl stared at him so?',questions:[{question:"Bill took the key with him to prevent Tom from returning.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"We know from the story that Tom had left there three days before.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Bill was surprised when he turned round, because the woman were there.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Although Bill said good night to the girl, she gave him a rude answer.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Bill didn't trust the girl because he had never seen her before.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"}]},{text:'The man sitting opposite Robert was the Financial Controller. Everybody called him "the FC"for short. He made all the decisions about money. Robert needed some more. That was why he had to see him. The two men did not get on very well. In fact, they had always disliked each other.\n  "Your request is out of the question,"the FC said. Robert had difficulty in controlling himself, but he managed somehow. He explained that he wanted the money in order to make more programmes.\n  "And why do you want to do that?" the FC asked sharply. Again, Robert almost lost his temper. "Because more and more people are listening to my department\'s programmes. There\'s great demand for them,"he answered.\n  The FC did not seem to believe him. But Robert had a report on the numbers of listeners to all EBC programmes. The FC became less confident. Robert threw the report down on the table and told him to read it.\n  The FC looked at it in silence. The figures proved that he had been wrong, but he did not want to admit it. "Well," he finally said, "I may have made a small mistake." Robert noticed the word "may."He got up to leave. But he had the feeling that he would get the money after all.',questions:[{question:"According to the story, the Financial Controller was a person in charge of EBC money.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"''...out of the question'' In the 2ndparagraph means without any question.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Robert decided to make more programmes because the FC disliked him.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"We don't know why more and more people were listening to Roberts programmes.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The Financial Controller won the argument in the end.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"}]},{text:'One day a policeman was taking a thief to the city police station. On their way they came to a shop where bread was sold.\n  "We have no food. And we must eat something on the train." said the thief. "It\'s a long way to the city and it will take us much time to get there. I\'ll go into this shop and buy some bread. Then you and I can eat it on the train. Wait here for me."\n  The policeman was glad, "I\'ll have some food on the train," he thought. "Be quick," he said to the thief. "We haven\'t much time."\n  The thief went into the shop, and the policeman waited in the street for a long time. He began to worry. He thought about the train, and at last he went into the shop.\n  "Where\'s that man who came in here to buy some bread?" asked the policeman.\n  "Oh, he went out by the back door," said the shopkeeper.\n  The policeman ran out but he could not see the thief. So he had to go back to his own station and tell the others about it. They were very angry with him, and he was very unhappy.\n  All the police of the town began to look for the thief again, and they soon caught him. They brought him back to the police station and called the same policeman."\n  "Now," said the officer, "take him to the city, and don\'t lose him again."\n  The policeman and the thief left the station, and they came to the same shop.\n  "Wait here," said the thief. "I want to go into that shop and buy some bread."\n  "Oh, no," said the policeman. "You did that once, and ran away. This time, I\'ll go into the shop and buy the bread, and you must wait here for me." ',questions:[{question:"The policeman was asked to look for the thief.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"When they got to the station, the policeman and the thief found a shop where bread was sold.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The thief entered the shop in order to steal some money.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"When the thief went into the shop, the policeman waited for him in the street.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The policeman might lose the thief for the second time.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:"Americans enjoy sports. The three national sports are American football, played in the fall; basketball, played in the winter; and baseball, played in the summer. The crowds at these events may surprise you. The World Series and the Super bowl will attract tens of thousands of fans to the stadium and there will be much shouting and cheering, but even if the spectator become very angry there is rare any violence.\n  Besides these big events, sports as recreation are enjoyed throughout the country. Golf, tennis, riding, sailing, surfing, jogging, and even parachuting, are popular recreational activities. You will find that the equipment for these sports can often be rented, so that even visitors are not excluded. Playing the sport you like is considered an essential part of a person's life. Luckily, the great natural resources such as lakes, mountains and vast seacoasts in the country allow Americans the space they need to enjoy themselves. ",questions:[{question:"Fall is the season of American football in the USA.       ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Americans enjoy big basketball events in winter.           ",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Fights between opposing teams usually happen in a crowded stadium.              ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Professional sports and school sports are discussed in the passage.          ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Sports events often lead to anger and violence among spectators.                  ",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"}]},{text:"Chess must be one of the oldest games in the world. An Arab traveller in India in the year 900 wrote that it was played 'long, long ago.' Chess was probably invented in India, and it has been played everywhere from Japan to Europe since 1400. The name 'chess' is interesting. When one player is attacking the other's king, he says in English, 'check'. When the king has been caught and cannot move anywhere, he says 'check mate'. These words come from Persian 'Shah mat' means 'the king is dead'. That is when the game is over, and one player has won.\n  Such an old game changes very slowly. The rules have not always been the same as they are now. For example, at one time the queen could only move one square at a time. Now she is the strongest piece on the board. It would be interesting to know why this has happened. Chess takes time and thought, but it is a game for all kinds of people. You don't have to be a champion in order to enjoy it. It is not always played by two people sitting at the same table. The first time the Americans beat the Russians was in a match played by radio. Some of the chess masters are able to play many people at the same time. The record was when one man played 400 games! It is said that some people played chess by post. This must make chess the slowest game in the world.",questions:[{question:"Chess was played in India long before 900.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"One player has won the game when he attacks the other player's king.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Chess is a game for all sorts of people.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Only two people can play chess sitting at the same table.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"According to the old rules of the game, the king could not move anywhere.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"}]},{text:"A characteristic of American culture that has become almost a tradition is to respect the self-made man - the man who has risen to the top through his own efforts, usually beginning by working with his hands. While the leader in business or industry or the college professor occupies a higher social position and commands greater respect in the community than the common laborer or even the skilled factory worker, he may take pains to point out that his father started life in America as a farmer or laborer of some sort.\n  This attitude toward manual (体力的) labor is now still seen in many aspects of American life. One is invited to dinner at a home that is not only comfortably but even luxuriously (豪华地) furnished and in which there is every evidence of the fact that the family has been able to afford foreign travel, expensive hobbies, and college education for the children; yet the hostess probably will cook the dinner herself, will serve it herself and will wash dishes afterward; furthermore,  the dinner will not consist merely of something quickly and easily assembled from contents of various cans and a cake or a pie bought at the nearby bakery. On the contrary, the hostess usually takes pride in careful preparation of special dishes. A professional may talk about washing the car, digging in his flowerbeds, painting the house. His wife may even help with these things, just as he often helps her with the dishwashing. The son who is away at college may wait on table and wash dishes for his living, or during the summer he may work with a construction gang on a highway in order to pay for his education. ",questions:[{question:"From Para. 1, we know that in America _________.",options:["people tend to have a high opinion of the self-made man","people can always rise to the top through their won efforts","college professors win great respect from common workers","people feel painful to mention their fathers as labors"],answer:"A"},{question:"According to the passage, the hostess cooks dinner herself mainly because _________.",options:["servants in America are hard to get. ","she takes pride in what she can do herself","she can hardly afford servants","it is easy to prepare a meal with canned food"],answer:"B"},{question:'The underlined expression "wait on table" in Para. 2 means "_________".',options:["work in a furniture shop","keep accounts for a bar","wait to lay the table","serve customers in a restaurant"],answer:"D"},{question:"The author’s attitude towards manual labor is _______.",options:["positive","negative","humorous","critical"],answer:"A"},{question:"Which of the following could be the best title of the passage? ",options:["A Respectable Self-made Family","American Attitude toward Manual Labor","Characteristics of American Culture","The Development of Manual Labor"],answer:"B"}]},{text:'It looks like a mobile phone, but the service is much cheaper. It acts like a mobile phone, but only in your own city. Beyond the city walls, it is useless.\n  "Little Smart", also called "Xiaolingtong", has always been compared to mobile phones. But actually it is more like one of those cordless phones(无绳电话) used around the home. The only difference is that this one reaches much further. It can travel across an entire city.\n  Cheap costs are the main reason for the success of Little Smart. It costs 25 yuan a month for the line and about 0.1 yuan per minute to use. What\'s more, unlike mobile phones, there is no fee for incoming calls. \n  But Little Smart is not really that smart. Users often complain about its bad service quality. "I couldn\'t receive a phone call if I was on a bus," said Li, a user in Beijing. "It worked fine when I stood still, but there were breaks in signal when I was moving."\n  Scientists are trying to make Little Smart more user-friendly. Messaging and Internet access (接入) have been added to the service. And the latest Little Smart handset even has color screen(彩屏). ',questions:[{question:"Little Smart is so popular in China because it looks like a mobile phone.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The cost of the service of Little Smart is about 0.1 yuan per minute to use.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Users are not satisfied with Little Smart because the quality of its service is bad.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:'The word "handset" in the last paragraph means appearance.',options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Scientists are trying to make Little Smart more user-friendly.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:"Who will stage the games?\n  Preparing for the Olympic Games is a huge undertaking (工程). Just like the athletes, the host city spends years getting ready for the event. Before deciding which city will host the Olympic Games, the International Olympic Committee (IOC) has to examine bids from all over the world. Bidding for the games begins about ten years in advance. Without preparing a very strong bid, a city will not win the competition to host the games. Beijing was chosen for the 2008 games from five bidders 一 Osaka, Paris, Toronto and Istanbul.\n  \n  Why does it take so long to prepare? \n  Building the infrastructure (基础设施) costs huge amounts of money. Holding the World Cup in 2002 in Japan and South Korea, for example, meant that ten new stadiums had to be built, as well as many hotels and an improved transport system. In Beijing, after winning the bid the government began major construction projects 一 the extension of the underground, the improvement of the airport and the building of new motorways. Each host city must also build an Olympic village for the athletes. By planting trees and creating parks, the city becomes more attractive for tourists.\n  \n  Why do countries want to host the Olympic Games?\n  Hosting the games has a major effect on the economy and brings international prestige(声望) to the country. Thousands and thousands of visitors come to the games and the host cities are permanently improved.  \n  ",questions:[{question:"Bidding for the Olympic Games usually starts one year before the games are really held.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Beijing was one of the five bidders for the 2008 games.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"The World Cup 2002 was held in China.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"Beijing started the improvement of the airport after winning the bid.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"Countries want to host the Olympic Games because it has a major effect on the economy.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:"Taking away a city's rubbish is a big job. Every day trucks come into a city to collect it. Most rubbish is made up of things we can't eat or use. If we kept these things, we would soon have a mountain of rubbish.\n  In some cities the rubbish is collected and taken outside the city to a dump. Often the city dump is placed where the ground is low or there is a big hole. The kitchen rubbish is broken into small pieces and sent into the sewage(污水,排水)system. The sewage system takes away the used water from toilets, bathtubs and other places.\n  To keep mice and flies away, some earth is used to cover the newly dumped rubbish. Later, grass may be planted on the rubbish-filled land. Finally, a house or a school may be built there, and then you'd never know that this had once been an old rubbish dump.\n  In other cities the rubbish is burnt in special places. The fire burns everything except the metal.Sometimes the metal can be used again in factories where things are made of metal. The food parts of rubbish are put in special piles where they slowly change into something called humus(腐殖质), which looks like black earth. It is rich with the kinds of things that feed plants and help make them grow. ",questions:[{question:"You can most probably read this kind of passage in a telephone book.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The main idea of the passage is to tell people to take useful things out of rubbish.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:'The underlined word "sewage" in the second paragraph means laundry.',options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"According to the passage, the food parts of rubbish can be used again to feed plants.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"We should take care of a used metal box by reusing and recycling it.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]},{text:'A group of frogs were traveling through the woods, and two of them fell into a deep pit. When the other frogs saw how deep the pit was, they told the two frogs that they were as good as dead. The two frogs ignored the comments and tried to jump up out of the pit with all their might. The other frogs kept telling them to stop, that they were as good as dead. Finally, one of the frogs took heed of(倾听) what the other frogs were saying and gave up. He fell down and died.\n  The other frog continued to jump as hard as he could. Once again, the crowd of frogs shouted  at him to stop the pain and just die. He jumped even harder and finally made it out. When he got out, the other frogs said, "Didn\'t you hear us?" The frog explained to them that he was a little deaf. He thought they were encouraging him the entire time.\n  This story teaches us two lessons:\n  1. There is power of life and death in the tongue. An encouraging word to someone who is down can lift him up and help him make it through the day.\n  2. A destructive word to someone who is down can be what it takes to kill him.\n  Be careful of what you say. The power of words is sometimes hard to understand because an encouraging word can go such a long way. Anyone can speak words that tend to rob another of the spirit to continue in difficult times. Special is the individual who will take the time to encourage another.',questions:[{question:'The expression "as good as" (in line 2, paragraph 1) means almost, practically.',options:["T","F"],answer:"A"},{question:"When other frogs told the two frogs there was no hope, the two frogs gave up their efforts immediately.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"One of the frogs fell down and died because he was so tired.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"The other frog managed to jump out of the pit because he was very strong physically.",options:["T","F"],answer:"B"},{question:"People should avoid saying destructive words to those who are in trouble.",options:["T","F"],answer:"A"}]}]},"50f0":function(e,t,o){"use strict";t["a"]=[{text:"Our school has a big library. It has many books on different subjects. Students can read books and newspapers in the __1__ room. They can also borrow books from the library. But they must __2__ them on time. If they lose books, they must pay for them. Miss Susan works in the library. She is very helpful and __3__ to the students.\n  One morning she was working at the desk when Amy hurried in. She told Miss Susan that she couldn't find the library book \" Harry Potter \"__4__. At that moment, Lucy came into the library with Amy's book. She found it in the classroom. Amy was very __5__. She thanked Lucy and said that she would be more careful from then on.",questions:[{options:["reading","return","happy","anywhere","kind"],answer:"A"},{options:["reading","return","happy","anywhere","kind"],answer:"B"},{options:["reading","return","happy","anywhere","kind"],answer:"E"},{options:["reading","return","happy","anywhere","kind"],answer:"D"},{options:["reading","return","happy","anywhere","kind"],answer:"C"}]},{text:"It was getting dark. Some children and two Canadian women were still ___1___ on the ice near a big hotel. They were having a good time.\n  Suddenly the ice broke. One of the boys fell into the water. The children shouted, \"Help! Help!\" They didn't know what to so. The two Canadian friends heard ___2___ and skated over to get the boy out of the water.\n  The ice was thin. The two Canadians fell into the water, too. But they tried their best to ___3___ the little boy. They knew they must be quick. If they didn't push him up onto the ice, he would soon die.\n  Many people ran over to help.Some of them had ropes and poles. A young man jumped into the water to save the ___4___ people.\n  The boy and the two Canadian women were out of water at last. One of the women didn't feel well. She was sent to the ___5___ at once. But she felt very happy because the boy was safe.",questions:[{options:["save","hospital","three","skating","them"],answer:"D"},{options:["save","hospital","three","skating","them"],answer:"E"},{options:["save","hospital","three","skating","them"],answer:"A"},{options:["save","hospital","three","skating","them"],answer:"C"},{options:["save","hospital","three","skating","them"],answer:"B"}]},{text:'A young man goes into a shop. He wants to buy a watch. He sees a watch that he likes, but the man in the shop ___1___ ninety pounds for it. At that time a boy comes into the shop, takes the watch out of the man\'s ___2___ and runs out. When the man in the shop runs out into the street, the boy is already among the people.\n  The young man goes ___3___. At the next corner he sees the boy with the stolen watch ___4___ his hand. "Would you like to buy a fine watch, sir?" he says in a low voice. "It is only fifty pounds." The young man pays at once, and goes back to his room. His friend takes a look ___5___ the watch and says, "This watch isn\'t worth even ten pounds. I think that they planned this together." When he hears this, the young man is very disappointed.',questions:[{options:["at","asks","hand","away","in"],answer:"B"},{options:["at","asks","hand","away","in"],answer:"C"},{options:["at","asks","hand","away","in"],answer:"D"},{options:["at","asks","hand","away","in"],answer:"E"},{options:["at","asks","hand","away","in"],answer:"A"}]},{text:"Water is very important to living things. Without water there can be ___1___ life on earth. All animals and plants need water. Man need water, too. We need water to drink, to cook our food and to clean ___2___.\n  Water ___3___ almost everywhere. Even in the driest part of the would there is some water in the air. You can not see it or feel it when it is part of the air. The water ___4___ seas and rivers is a liquid. The water in the air is not a liquid but a gas.\n  Clouds are made of water. They may ___5__ made of very small drops of water. Water, you have found,is very useful, so we must save water. ",questions:[{options:["ourselves","is found","be","in","no"],answer:"E"},{options:["ourselves","is found","be","in","no"],answer:"A"},{options:["ourselves","is found","be","in","no"],answer:"B"},{options:["ourselves","is found","be","in","no"],answer:"D"},{options:["ourselves","is found","be","in","no"],answer:"C"}]},{text:"Man has always wanted to fly. Even as long as eight hundred years ago, an Englishman had tried. He made a pair of __1__ from chicken feathers and fixed them to his shoulders. Then he jumped from a tall building. As you can imagine, he did not fly very far. __2__, he fell to the ground and broke several bones. The first real attempt at flying took place in France in 1783. The two Mongolian brothers knew that hot air rose. If they could fill a large balloon with hot air, they thought it would rise into the air and __3__. They were right. They made a very large hot air balloon of cloth and paper. It measured ten meters in diameter. They filled it with hot air and the balloon got two hundred meters into the air. It fell to earth about three kilometers __4__.\n  At the next attempt, they arranged for a balloon to carry passengers. We do not know what the passengers felt about the trip as they were a cock, a duck, and a sheep. But we __5__ know that the trip lasted eight minutes and the animals landed safely.",questions:[{options:["Instead","wings","do","away","fly"],answer:"B"},{options:["Instead","wings\t","do\t","away","fly"],answer:"A"},{options:["Instead","wings","do","away","fly"],answer:"E"},{options:["Instead","wings","do","away","fly"],answer:"D"},{options:["Instead","wings","do","away","fly"],answer:"C"}]},{text:"Tom Smith was a writer. He wrote detective stories __1__ magazines. One evening he could not find an end for a story. He sat __2__ his typewriter in front of him; but he had no ideas. So he decided to go to the cinema.\n  When he came back, he saw that he had had a visitor. Someone had broken into his flat. The man had had a drink, smoked several of Tom's cigarettes and had read his story. The visitor left Tom a note: \n  I __3__ your story and I don't think much of it. Please read my suggestions and then you can finish it. By the way, I am a thief. I am not going to steal __4__ tonight. But if you become a successful writer, I will be back!\n  Tom read his suggestions. Then he sat __5__ and wrote the rest of the story. He is still not a successful writer, and he is waiting for his thief to return. Before he goes out in the evening, he always leaves a half - finished story near his typewriter.",questions:[{options:["have read","anything","down","with","for"],answer:"E"},{options:["have read","anything","down","with","for"],answer:"D"},{options:["have read","anything","down","with","for"],answer:"A"},{options:["have read","anything","down","with","for"],answer:"B"},{options:["have read","anything","down","with","for"],answer:"C"}]},{text:'A miser(守财奴)sold all that he had and bought a lump of gold, ___1___ he buried in a hole in the ground by the side of an old wall and ___2___ to look at daily. One of his workmen observed his frequent visits to the spot and decided to watch his movements. He soon discovered the secret of the hidden treasure, came to the lump of gold, and ___3___ it. The Miser, on his next visit, found the hole empty and began to tear his hair and to cry. A neighbor, seeing him overcome with grief悲伤)and learning the cause, said, "Go and take a stone, and place it in the ___4___, and fancy that the gold is still lying there. It will do you quite the same service; for when the gold was there, you did not ___5___ the slightest use of it." ',questions:[{options:["make","which","hole","stole","went"],answer:"B"},{options:["make","which","hole","stole","went"],answer:"E"},{options:["make","which","hole","stole","went"],answer:"D"},{options:["make","which","hole","stole","went"],answer:"C"},{options:["make","which","hole","stole","went"],answer:"A"}]},{text:'One night, a thief broke into an old man\'s house. He ___1___ a noise and woke up the old man and his wife. The husband told his wife to be silent, while he said loudly, "My dear, these days thieves are cleverer. If they take ___2___ their clothes and put them on the table, the people in the room will fall asleep and can\'t wake up."\n  When the thief ___3___this, he took off his clothes at once and was ready to set out to work. At this___4___, the husband suddenly shouted in a loud voice:"Stop thief! Stop thief!" The thief was very frightened. He ran away as fast as be could and ___5___ his clothes on the table.',questions:[{options:["made","moment","off","left","heard"],answer:"A"},{options:["made","moment","off","left","heard"],answer:"C"},{options:["made","moment","off","left","heard"],answer:"E"},{options:["made","moment","off","left","heard"],answer:"B"},{options:["made","moment","off","left","heard"],answer:"D"}]},{text:"The old lady was eighty today. She had __1__ on her best dress. Perhaps Myra might come. After all, eighty was a special birthday, another decade lived or __2__ just as you chose to look at it.\n  Even if Myra did not come, she would send a present. The old lady was sure of that. Two spots of color brightened her cheeks. She was excited   __3__ a child. She would enjoy her day.\n  Yesterday Mrs. Morrison had given the flat an extra clean, and today she had brought a card and __4__ marigolds when she came to do the breakfast. Mrs. Grant downstairs had __5__ a cake, and in the afternoon she was going down there to tea.",questions:[{options:["endured","like","a bunch of","put","made"],answer:"D"},{options:["endured","like","a bunch of","put","made"],answer:"A"},{options:["endured","like","a bunch of","put","made"],answer:"B"},{options:["endured","like","a bunch of","put","made"],answer:"C"},{options:["endured","like","a bunch of","put","made"],answer:"E"}]},{text:'An old man went to the hospital. When the doctor came to __1__ him, he said, "Well, Mr. Jones, you\'re going to have some injections(注射), and then you\'ll feel __2__. A nurse will come and give you the first one this evening, and then you\'ll get another one tomorrow morning."\n  In the evening a young nurse came to Mr. Jones\' bed and said to him, "I\'m going to give you your first injection now, Mr. Jones. Where do you want it?"\n  The old man was surprised. He __3__ the nurse for several seconds, and then he said, "Nobody\'s ever let me choose that before. Are you really going to let me choose now?"\n  "Yes, Mr. Jones," the nurse answered. She was __4__. "Where do you want it?"\n  "Well, then," the old man answered __5__ a smile, "I want it in your left arm, please."\n  ',questions:[{options:["looked at","in a hurry","see","with","much better"],answer:"C"},{options:["look at","in a hurry","see","with","much better"],answer:"E"},{options:["look at","in a hurry","see","with","much better"],answer:"A"},{options:["look at","in a hurry","see","with","much better"],answer:"B"},{options:["look at","in a hurry","see","with","much better"],answer:"D"}]},{text:'Last Tuesday I took my two daughters, aged five and seven, to town by car. It began to rain hard, so I decided I would leave the children in the car ___1___ I rushed into a shop. I warned the girls not to touch anything and told them I would be ___2___ within a few minutes. Then I locked all the doors and left them happily looking out of the window.\n  I returned to the car in less than five minutes but the girls had disappeared! I could hardly believe my ___3___. The car doors were still locked, the windows tightly shut and on the back seat ___4___ only two coats. Being frightened, I ran to the corner of the street where there was no sign of them. I ___5___ up to an old lady nearby and asked whether she had seen two small girls, but she said "No".',questions:[{options:["back","before","were","eyes","rushed"],answer:"B"},{options:["back","before","were","eyes","rushed"],answer:"A"},{options:["back","before","were","eyes","rushed"],answer:"D"},{options:["back","before","were","eyes","rushed"],answer:"C"},{options:["back","before","were","eyes","rushed"],answer:"E"}]},{text:"Many people buy suitcases to carry their luggage when they go abroad on holiday and never take the trouble to find out whether they will be __1__ to survive the journey. Whatever case you buy - and obviously the more you pay for it, the better it is likely to be - you should be careful __2__ too much into it. A lot of passengers __3__ and then the locks break. Some people think manufacturers should say how much the case can carry. But the manufacturers say it depends __4__ the quality of the case. A cheap case, __5__ has been badly made, will obviously not last as long as an expensive one. ",questions:[{options:["not to pack","do so","which","strong enough","on"],answer:"D"},{options:["not to pack","do so","which","strong enough","on"],answer:"A"},{options:["not to pack","do so","which","strong enough","on"],answer:"B"},{options:["not to pack","do so","which","strong enough","on"],answer:"E"},{options:["not to pack","do so","which","strong enough","on"],answer:"C"}]},{text:"When someone asks me what business I am in. My face feels hot. I envy (嫉妒) people who can say that they are writers, bookkeepers and doctors. All these jobs speak for themselves.\n  I really do make a living by __1__, and a good one, too. I can laugh like a king or like a schoolboy. It is a skill that I have learned, like the skill of mending shoes. Whenever and however laughter is needed - I am asked to do __2__. I laugh like a bus driver or a shopkeeper. I laugh sadly, kindly and happily.\n  I need __3__ point out that a job of this kind is tiring. I spend most evenings in nightclubs. My job is to laugh during the weaker part of the show. My loud, hearty laugher must be timed carefully. It must not come too soon, __4__ neither must it be too late.\n  I go through life quietly. I can copy the laughter of others. I can laugh in many different ways. But I'm not sure that I have ever heard the sound of __5__ own laugh.",questions:[{options:["hardly","my","but","it","laughing"],answer:"E"},{options:["hardly","my","but","it","laughing"],answer:"D"},{options:["hardly","my","but","it","laughing"],answer:"A"},{options:["hardly","my","but","it","laughing"],answer:"C"},{options:["hardly","my","but","it","laughing"],answer:"B"}]},{text:"I have been in London for two weeks. I don't speak English well at all. I have great difficulty in understanding people. In fact I don't catch a thing they say. I find their pronunciation is __1__ strange for me to understand, and they speak __2__ that I can't keep up with them. When I am on a bus, I ask the conductor something. He answers, but I don't understand. So he says it slowly in a high __3__, I still don't understand it. Then he gets angry and goes away.\n  But I haven't lost heart. I still enjoy __4__ English. I must keep on working hard __5__ it. I believe I'll speak English well soon.",questions:[{options:["voice","too","speaking","at","so fast"],answer:"B"},{options:["voice","too","speaking","at","so fast"],answer:"E"},{options:["voice","too","speaking","at","so fast"],answer:"A"},{options:["voice","too","speaking","at","so fast"],answer:"C"},{options:["voice","too","speaking","at","so fast"],answer:"D"}]},{text:'Many people have to work at weekends. Some people do not mind, others think it is terrible.\n  One man thinks that working at weekends can be __1__. He is George Smith. Mr. Smith works in an office, in Brighton, England.\n  On Saturday, May 24, 1986, he went to the office to do some work. After he __2__ the lift, it stopped between floors. Mr. Smith could not get out of the lift. He began to shout, but no one heard him. Then Mr. Smith remembered that it was a holiday in England. No one was going to come to work until Tuesday.\n  There was __3__ for Mr. Smith to do. He had to wait until one of his workmates came to work and found him. With nothing to eat or drink, Mr. Smith was very hungry and had to sleep most of the time.\n  Early on Tuesday morning, one of his workmates came into work and found the lift __4__. When the lift was opened, Mr. Smith came out cold, weak, and tired. He had been in the lift for over 60 hours!\n  Now Mr. Smith says, "I only use the lift if they have __5__ in them."\n  ',questions:[{options:["nothing","got into","was not working","telephones","dangerous"],answer:"E"},{options:["nothing","got into","was not working","telephones","dangerous"],answer:"B"},{options:["nothing","got into","was not working","telephones","dangerous"],answer:"A"},{options:["nothing","got into","was not working","telephones","dangerous"],answer:"C"},{options:["nothing","got into","was not working","telephones","dangerous"],answer:"D"}]},{text:'One day Mr. Parker said to himself, "I haven\'t seen my brother David __1__ a long time, and he\'s living in a new house now. I\'m going to drive there and see him this afternoon."\n  He took his brother\'s address, got into his car and started out. He drove for a long time, but he didn\'t find the house __2__ he stopped and asked somebody to help him.\n  "Go straight __3__ this road for two miles(英里)," the man said, "then turn left, and then take the second road on the right."\n  Mr. Parker went straight along the road and turned left after two miles, but then he got lost again. He drove for __4__ mile, and at last he saw a road on his right and stopped. A woman was coming __5__ him, so he said to her, "Excuse me, is this the second road on the right?"\n  ',questions:[{options:["so","for","towards","along","another"],answer:"B"},{options:["so","for","towards","along","another"],answer:"A"},{options:["so","for","towards","along","another"],answer:"D"},{options:["so","for","towards","along","another"],answer:"E"},{options:["so","for","towards","along","another"],answer:"C"}]},{text:"If you were to begin a new job tomorrow, you would bring with you some basic strengths and weaknesses. Success or __1__ in your work would depend, to a great extent, __2__ your ability to use your strengths and weaknesses to the best advantage. Of the utmost importance is your attitude. A person __3__ begins a job convinced that he isn't going to like it or is sure that he is going to exhibit a weakness which can only hinder his success. On the other hand, a person who is secure in his belief that he is probably as capable __4__ doing the work as anyone else and who is willing to make a cheerful attempt at it possesses a certain strength of purpose. The chances are that he will do well. Having the most important skills for a particular job is strength. __5__ those skills is obviously a weakness. A bookkeeper who can't add and a carpenter who can't cut a straight line with a saw are hopeless cases.",questions:[{options:["who","failure","on","Lacking","of"],answer:"B"},{options:["who","failure","on","Lacking","of"],answer:"C"},{options:["who","failure","on","Lacking","of"],answer:"A"},{options:["who","failure","on","Lacking","of"],answer:"E"},{options:["who","failure","on","Lacking","of"],answer:"D"}]},{text:"George Stephenson was born in 1781. He was __1__ a poor English worker's family. His father looked after a steam engine. He worked hard indeed, __2__ he could not support his family. Where could he get the money to send George to school? George began to learn his ABC when he was seventeen. On his 18th birthday, he could write his own name.\n  George had to work when he was only a small child. The work was much too hard __3__ him. He worked for 12 hours every day. After a day's work he often felt __4__ tired to stand.\n  He worked and studied very hard. He spent all this time learning about the steam engine.\n  __5__ he studied hard, he invented many things. The railway locomotive(火车头)was the greatest one of them.\n  ",questions:[{options:["too","from","for","Because","but"],answer:"B"},{options:["too","from","for","Because","but"],answer:"E"},{options:["too","from","for","Because","but"],answer:"C"},{options:["too","from","for","Because","but"],answer:"A"},{options:["too","from","for","Because","but"],answer:"D"}]},{text:'Jack lost his Job last week. It was difficult for him to find another ___1___. Somebody told him that it was possible to get a new one in a town two hundred kilometers away. He decided to get there ___2___. So he went to the railway station and got on a train. He was the only one in the car(车厢). The train started. Suddenly a man came in ___3___ a gun and said to him, "Your money or your life!" Jack sat there without standing up. \n  "I ___4___ any money," Jack answered. \n  "Then why are you so afraid of me?" the man asked angrily. \n  "Because I ___5___ you were the conductor, and I didn\'t buy a ticket," answered Jack. ',questions:[{options:["one","don't have","thought","with","by train"],answer:"A"},{options:["one","don't have","thought","with","by train"],answer:"E"},{options:["one","don't have","thought","with","by train"],answer:"D"},{options:["one","don't have","thought","with","by train"],answer:"B"},{options:["one","don't have","thought","with","by train"],answer:"C"}]},{text:"Two years ago, my husband left a bike for me. \n  If you live in a town, it is often faster than a car and don't have to worry about parking(停车). You can ___1___ it anywhere. Because it has a seat at the back and a basket at the front, I can take my small daughter when it is cold and it is snowing hard. It also can be dangerous. You must be ___2___ on a bike. Accidents are not the only problem. One day I went ___3___ and when I came back, I couldn't find my front wheel. It was a long walk to the bike shop! Now I have three strong locks.\n  Sometimes my husband uses my bike for short trips. He is not good at ___4___ bikes, but he says it is better than waiting for a bus. He still likes his car for longer trips, but I think that all this sitting down is making him fat. ___5___ my bike I got a lot of exercise and fresh air, and makes me feel much healthy. ",questions:[{options:["shopping","buy","On","careful ","riding"],answer:"B"},{options:["shopping","buy","On","careful ","riding"],answer:"D"},{options:["shopping","buy","On","careful ","riding"],answer:"A"},{options:["shopping","buy","On","careful ","riding"],answer:"E"},{options:["shopping","buy","On","careful ","riding"],answer:"C"}]},{text:"A: Hi, Sun Yan! What are you busy with these days?\n  B: I'm busy ___1___ for the Spring Festival.\n  A: What do you mean by the Spring Festival?\n  B: Don't you know about the Spring Festival? It's ___2___ your Christmas holiday. It's the most important holiday in China.\n  A: Oh, I see. ___3___ is the holiday?\n  B: About one week long.\n  A: What do you usually do during the holiday?\n  B: Lots of things, such as eating and drinking, playing majiang, going to movies and temple fairs (庙会), visiting relatives and friends   and so on. In many places people like to set off firecrackers (鞭炮). It is very interesting. But now it isn't allowed in some big cities because it is not safe.\n  A: Do you eat special food for the holiday?\n  B: Yes, we eat dumplings.\n  A: Do children like the holiday?\n  B: Sure. Children can have delicious food and wear new clothes. They can also get some money from their parents.\n  A: What is that money for?\n  B: This money is given to children for good luck by their parents or other senior people. Children can use the money ___4___ a lot of things for themselves.\n  A: That's very interesting. Thank you for ___5___ me so much about the Spring Festival.\n  B: It's pleasure.",questions:[{options:["How long","preparing","like","telling","to buy"],answer:"B"},{options:["How long","preparing","like","telling","to buy"],answer:"C"},{options:["How long","preparing","like","telling","to buy"],answer:"A"},{options:["How long","preparing","like","telling","to buy"],answer:"E"},{options:["How long","preparing","like","telling","to buy"],answer:"D"}]},{text:"A house in Clarktown caught fire on Christmas Eve, 1982. The woman who lived in the house was already in her eighties. Being in poor health, she had trouble in __1__ even when things were fine. With her house burning down around her, she was not able to go __2__. The smoke made her choke (窒息). The fire was very hot. Without quick help she would have died.\n  Fire fighters got to the house. They started to put the fire out. They did not know the old woman was still __3__. The people heard her crying for help. The fire was still very hot and there was lots of smoke.\n  A man dressed like Santa Claus(圣诞老人) was passing by. He was on his way to give gifts to poor families. Hardly had he heard the old woman' cry when he ran into the burning house. After a while he rushed out with the old woman on his back and came to her safety. Then, as __4__ as he had done that, the man left. No one knew the real name of the hero who had saved the old woman's life.\n  The man went on and took the gifts to the poor children. He did not return home until it was dark. He told his __5__ what had happened. She decided that she did not need to keep the story a secret. She told people that Santa Claus was actually David Rodriguez, her husband. Mr. Rodriguez is a music teacher when he is not playing Santa Claus.",questions:[{options:["inside","walking","wife","anywhere","quickly"],answer:"B"},{options:["inside","walking","wife","anywhere","quickly"],answer:"D"},{options:["inside","walking","wife","anywhere","quickly"],answer:"A"},{options:["inside","walking","wife","anywhere","quickly"],answer:"E"},{options:["inside","walking","wife","anywhere","quickly"],answer:"C"}]},{text:"What do we know about the sea? We know that it looks very beautiful when the sun is shining on it. We also learn that it can be very terrible when there is a strong wind. What __1__ things do we know about it?\n  The first thing to remember is that the sea is very big. Look at the map of the world, there is __2__ sea than land. The sea covers three quarters of the world.\n  Some parts of the sea __3__ very shallow. But some places are very deep. There is one place near Japan. It is nearly 11 kilometers deep. The __4__ mountain in the world is about 9 kilometers high. If we put the mountain into the sea at that place, there would be 2 kilometers of water above it!\n  The sea is salty. There is one sea called the Dead Sea. It is very salty. It is __5__ salty that swimmers cannot sink! Fish cannot live in the Dead Sea.",questions:[{options:["so","other","highest","are","more"],answer:"B"},{options:["so","other","highest","are","more"],answer:"E"},{options:["so","other","highest","are","more"],answer:"D"},{options:["so","other","highest","are","more"],answer:"C"},{options:["so","other","highest","are","more"],answer:"A"}]},{text:"In the American family the husband and wife usually share important decision-making. When the children are old enough, they take part as well. Foreigners are often surprised by the permissiveness (宽容) of American parents. Children are often allowed to do pretty much __1__ they wish without strict control by their parents. Children are encouraged to be __2__ at an early age. Some people believe that American parents carry this freedom too far. Others think that a strong parental image would not suit American values. Because Americans emphasize the importance of independence, young people are expected to break away from their families by the time they have __3__ their late teens or early twenties. This pattern of independence often raises serious problems for the aging parents of a small family. The average American is expected to live __4__ the age of 70. The job-retirement age is usually 65. The children have left home, married, and __5__ their own households. Often the major problem of many elderly couples is not economic, but they feel useless and lonely with neither an occupation nor a close family ties.",questions:[{options:["reached","what","set up","beyond","independent"],answer:"B"},{options:["reached","what","set up","beyond","independent"],answer:"E"},{options:["reached","what","set up","beyond","independent"],answer:"A"},{options:["reached","what","set up","beyond","independent"],answer:"D"},{options:["reached","what","set up","beyond","independent"],answer:"C"}]},{text:'Mary and Peter were having a picnic with some friends near a river when Mary shouted, "Look! That\'s a spaceship up there and it\'s going to land here."\n  Frightened by the strange spaceship, __1__ of the young people got into their cars and drove away as quickly as possible. Peter loved Mary and always stayed close to her. They, more __2__ than frightened, watched the spaceship land and saw a door open. When nobody came out, they went to look into it. In the center of the floor, there was a pile of food. Peter followed Mary into the spaceship and did not __3__ the door close behind him. The temperature fell rapidly and the two young people lost their consciousness.\n  When they came to life, they were surprised to see that they were back by the river again. The spaceship had gone. There car was nearby.\n  "What happened?" asked Mary. Peter scratched his head, saying slowly, "Don\'t ask me. Perhaps we had a __4__. Come on. It\'s time to go home."\n  After driving about fifty meters, they found their way blocked by a thick wall made of something like glass. On the other side of the wall, a few strange beings stopped to __5__ it and read a notice which, translated into English, said: "New arrivals at Zoo: a pair of earth inhabitants in their natural surroundings with their house on wheels."',questions:[{options:["most","hear","curious","look through","dream"],answer:"A"},{options:["most","hear","curious","look through","dream"],answer:"C"},{options:["most","hear","curious","look through","dream"],answer:"B"},{options:["most","hear","curious","look through","dream"],answer:"E"},{options:["most","hear","curious","look through","dream"],answer:"D"}]}]},"56d7":function(e,t,o){"use strict";o.r(t);o("cadf"),o("551c"),o("f751"),o("097d");var n=o("2b0e"),a=function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,o=e._self._c||t;return o("div",{attrs:{id:"app"}},[o("router-view")],1)},s=[],i=(o("7c55"),o("2877")),r={},h=Object(i["a"])(r,a,s,!1,null,null,null),l=h.exports,d=o("8c4f"),u=function(){var e=this,t=e.$createElement,o=e._self._c||t;return o("div",{staticClass:"home"},[o("router-link",{attrs:{to:"/english"}},[e._v("英语")]),o("router-link",{attrs:{to:"/computer"}},[e._v("计算机")])],1)},w=[],m=(o("8e6e"),o("456d"),o("ac6a"),o("bd86")),p=o("75fc"),c=o("d289"),y=o("309d"),_=o("50f0");function g(e,t){var o=Object.keys(e);if(Object.getOwnPropertySymbols){var n=Object.getOwnPropertySymbols(e);t&&(n=n.filter(function(t){return Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptor(e,t).enumerable})),o.push.apply(o,n)}return o}function f(e){for(var t=1;t<arguments.length;t++){var o=null!=arguments[t]?arguments[t]:{};t%2?g(o,!0).forEach(function(t){Object(m["a"])(e,t,o[t])}):Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptors?Object.defineProperties(e,Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptors(o)):g(o).forEach(function(t){Object.defineProperty(e,t,Object.getOwnPropertyDescriptor(o,t))})}return e}var b={name:"home",data:function(){return{dxlist:[],wxlist:[],ydlist:[],A_Z:["A","B","C","D","E","F"],submit:!1,score:0}},methods:{getDanXuan:function(){var e=Object(p["a"])(c["a"]);this.dxlist=[];for(var t=0;t<10;t++){var o=~~(Math.random()*e.length);this.dxlist.push(f({},e[o],{xx:""})),e.splice(o,1)}},getYueDu:function(){var e=Object(p["a"])(y["a"]);this.ydlist=[];for(var t=0;t<3;t++){var o=~~(Math.random()*e.length);this.ydlist.push({text:e[o].text,questions:e[o].questions.map(function(e){return f({},e,{xx:""})})}),e.splice(o,1)}},getWanXing:function(){var e=Object(p["a"])(_["a"]);this.wxlist=[];for(var t=0;t<1;t++){var o=~~(Math.random()*e.length);this.wxlist.push({text:e[o].text,questions:e[o].questions.map(function(e){return f({},e,{xx:""})})}),e.splice(o,1)}},submitFn:function(){var e=this;this.score=0,this.dxlist.forEach(function(t){t.xx===t.answer&&(e.score+=2)}),this.wxlist.forEach(function(t){t.questions.forEach(function(t){t.xx===t.answer&&(e.score+=2)})}),this.ydlist.forEach(function(t){t.questions.forEach(function(t){t.xx===t.answer&&(e.score+=2)})}),this.submit=!0},reset:function(){this.score=0,this.submit=!1,this.getDanXuan(),this.getWanXing(),this.getYueDu()}},created:function(){this.getDanXuan(),this.getWanXing(),this.getYueDu()}},k=b,v=(o("c6a3"),Object(i["a"])(k,u,w,!1,null,"6cc38c9e",null)),T=v.exports;n["default"].use(d["a"]);var q=new d["a"]({mode:"hash",base:"/examination/dist/",routes:[{path:"/",name:"home",component:T},{path:"/english",name:"english",component:function(){return o.e("english").then(o.bind(null,"2e67"))}},{path:"/computer",name:"computer",component:function(){return o.e("about").then(o.bind(null,"9d6d"))}}]}),I=o("2f62");n["default"].use(I["a"]);var A=new I["a"].Store({state:{},mutations:{},actions:{}}),B=o("5c96"),F=o.n(B);o("0fae");n["default"].config.productionTip=!1,n["default"].use(F.a),new n["default"]({router:q,store:A,render:function(e){return e(l)}}).$mount("#app")},"5c48":function(e,t,o){},"7c55":function(e,t,o){"use strict";var n=o("5c48"),a=o.n(n);a.a},c6a3:function(e,t,o){"use strict";var n=o("e7a4"),a=o.n(n);a.a},d289:function(e,t,o){"use strict";t["a"]=[{question:"I didn’t know what to do, but then an idea suddenly ________ to me.",options:["appeared","happened","occurred","emerged"],answer:"C"},{question:"A pair of spectacles ________ what I need at the moment.",options:["is","are","has","have"],answer:"A"},{question:"You had better ________ a doctor as soon as possible.",options:["seeing","saw","see","seen"],answer:"C"},{question:"- Do you want to wait?\n    - Five days ________ too long for me to wait.",options:["was","were","is","are"],answer:"C"},{question:"I fell and hurt myself while I ________ basketball yesterday.",options:["was playing","am playing","play","played"],answer:"A"},{question:"Don’t forget ________ the window before leaving the room.",options:["to have closed","to close","having closed","closing"],answer:"B"},{question:"The top of the Great Wall is ________ for five horses to go side by side.",options:["wide","so wide","wide enough","enough wide"],answer:"C"},{question:"It was well known that Thomas Edison _____ the electric lamp.",options:["discovered","invented","found","developed"],answer:"B"},{question:"We’ve missed the last bus. I’m afraid we have no ________ but to take a taxi.",options:["way","choice","possibility","selection"],answer:"B"},{question:"Nancy is considered to be ________ the other students in her class.",options:["less intelligent","the most intelligent","intelligent as well","as intelligent as"],answer:"D"},{question:"Australia is one of the few countries ____ people drive on the left of the road.",options:["which","that","where","on which"],answer:"C"},{question:"The higher the temperature, _____the liquid evaporates.",options:["the faster","the more fast","the slower","the more slower"],answer:"A"},{question:"____ you know, David has been well lately.",options:["Which","As","What","When"],answer:"B"},{question:"The harder you study, ____ you will learn.",options:["much","many","the more","much more"],answer:"C"},{question:"She wonders ____will happen to her private life in the future.",options:["that","it","this","what"],answer:"D"},{question:"The grey building is the place where the workers live, and the white building is the place where the spare parts _____.",options:["are producing","are produced","produced","being produced"],answer:"B"},{question:"They got there an hour _____than the others.",options:["early","much early","more early","earlier"],answer:"D"},{question:"Sunday is the day ____ people usually don’t go to work.",options:["when","which","in which","that"],answer:"A"},{question:"We worked hard and completed the task _____.",options:["in the time","on the time","ahead of time","before time"],answer:"C"},{question:"I like the teacher _____classes are very interesting and creative.",options:["which","who","whose","what"],answer:"C"},{question:"When Lily came home at 5 p.m. yesterday, her mother _____dinner in the kitchen.",options:["cooked","was cooking","cooks","has cooked"],answer:"B"},{question:"I didn’t expect you to turn _____ at the meeting yesterday.",options:["up","to","out","over"],answer:"A"},{question:"The young lady coming over to us _____ our English teacher; the way she walks tells us that!",options:["must be","can be","would be","could be"],answer:"A"},{question:"Once environmental damage ______, it takes many years for the system to recover.",options:["is to do","does","had done","is done"],answer:"D"},{question:"Eggs, though rich in nourishments, have ______ of fat.",options:["a large number","the large number","a large amount","the large amount"],answer:"C"},{question:"I don’t know the park, but it's______ to be quite beautiful.",options:["said","told","spoken","talked"],answer:"A"},{question:"Jane’s dress is similar in design ______ her sister’s.",options:["like","with","to","as"],answer:"C"},{question:"The manager will not _________ us to use his car.",options:["have","let","agree","allow"],answer:"D"},{question:"Neither John ______ his father was able to wake up early enough to catch the morning train.",options:["nor","or","but","and"],answer:"A"},{question:"_______ these honours he received a sum of money.",options:["Except","But","Besides","Outside"],answer:"C"},{question:"Mike is better than Peter _______ swimming．",options:["for","at","on","in"],answer:"B"},{question:"His salary as a driver is much higher than ________.",options:["a porter","is a porter","as a porter","that of a porter"],answer:"D"},{question:"He opened the letter and it contained ________.",options:["an important information","some important informations","many important information","some important information"],answer:"D"},{question:"He has been writing for 3 years, but being a writer is not his ________.",options:["chance","choice","change","character"],answer:"B"},{question:"They have never heard any _______.",options:["a customer complaint","the customer's complaints","customer's complaint","the customers' complaints"],answer:"C"},{question:"He is not a child ________.",options:["no more","no longer","any much","any more"],answer:"D"},{question:"We've missed the last bus. I'm afraid we have no ________ but to take a taxi.",options:["way","choice","possibility","selection   "],answer:"B"},{question:"The retired man is used to ________ his two dogs early in the morning.",options:["exercise","exercising","exercised","exercises "],answer:"B"},{question:"It was not ________ midnight that they discovered the children were not in their bedroom.",options:["before","at","after","until  "],answer:"D"},{question:"Young ________ he is, he knows how to get along with others.",options:["like","as","although","however"],answer:"B"},{question:"Could you show me where the _______ shoes are?",options:["Women","womens","woman","women's"],answer:"D"},{question:"He succeeded ______ out a lot of things entirely new in the world.",options:["in working","to work ","working","at working "],answer:"A"},{question:"It took me a long time to ________ the disappointment of failing the exam.",options:["get over","get up","get into","get down "],answer:"A"},{question:"She _______ 100 pages of the book today.",options:["has already read","already reads","already read","was already read"],answer:"A"},{question:"He has been ______ for nearly three weeks after the death of his dear pet.",options:["sad\t\t\t\t","satisfied\t\t\t","evil\t\t\t\t","joyful"],answer:"A"},{question:"One cannot learn a foreign language well ______ he studies hard.",options:["unless\t\t\t","if\t\t\t\t","as\t\t\t","when"],answer:"A"},{question:"A large number of people ______ present at the meeting, which was out of our expectation.",options:["was\t\t\t\t","were\t\t\t\t","have\t\t\t\t","has"],answer:"B"},{question:"When the girls saw the funny man, they couldn't ____ laughing.",options:["keep from\t\t\t\t\t","keep on","keep away\t\t\t\t\t","keep at"],answer:"A"},{question:"We are glad that we finally managed to get into contact ________ them.",options:["at\t\t\t\t","on\t\t\t","from\t\t\t","with"],answer:"D"},{question:"This kind of plant ______ a lot of water at all times.",options:["assumes\t\t\t","limits \t\t\t\t","produces \t\t\t","requires"],answer:"D"},{question:"Look! Here _______ the famous player.",options:["comes\t\t\t","come\t\t\t","had come\t\t","coming"],answer:"A"},{question:"Uncle Sam sent him a _______ bicycle as a birthday present.",options:["red sports new           ","sports new red             ","new sports red           ","new red sports"],answer:"D"},{question:"I couldn't find my English-Chinese dictionary _______.",options:["anywhere        ","everywhere      ","nowhere        ","somewhere  "],answer:"A"},{question:"The plane was about to _______, and yet I left my ticket behind.",options:["take off\t\t\t\t\t\t","take on\t\t \t","take up\t\t\t\t\t\t","take in"],answer:"A"},{question:"John succeeded _______ what he wanted.",options:["to get     ","to getting         ","in getting          ","and getting       "],answer:"C"},{question:"The accident was ______ to careless driving.",options:["for     ","likely     ","due     ","because"],answer:"C"},{question:"With a good command of reading skills, most students can manage to read _______as they could the year before.",options:["as twice fast","as fast as twice","as twice as fast","twice as fast"],answer:"D"},{question:"Some famous singers live on the _______from their record sales. ",options:["salary","price","bill","income"],answer:"D"},{question:"__________of them thinks that is a good idea.",options:["Anyone","No one","None","Someone"],answer:"C"},{question:"Don't be too _______about things you're not supposed to know.\t\t",options:["strange","amusing","curious","conscious"],answer:"C"},{question:"It was in 1969 ______the American astronauts succeeded in landing on the moon. ",options:["when","the moment","which","that"],answer:"D"},{question:"_______people in the world are sending information by e-mail every day. ",options:["Several million","Many millions","Several millions","Many million"],answer:"A"},{question:"He _______less time reading stories about film stars than before.",options:["takes","spends","costs","pays"],answer:"B"},{question:"Selecting a mobile phone for personal use is no easy task because technology _______so rapidly.",options:["is changing","has been changed","will have changed","will change"],answer:"A"},{question:"The taxi driver always reminds passengers to _______their belongings when they leave the car. \t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t",options:["keep","catch","hold","take"],answer:"D"},{question:"Little Tom is used to getting up _______eight every morning.",options:["at","on","in","of"],answer:"A"},{question:"If the doctor had been available, the child ____________.",options:["would not die","could not have died","might not die","should not have died"],answer:"B"},{question:"If Mary _______shopping this afternoon, please ask her to write a shopping list first.",options:["will go","goes","went","has gone"],answer:"B"},{question:"These desks and chairs ______to the children in the mountain villages next week.",options:["are sent","will send","have sent","will be sent"],answer:"D"},{question:"Every society has its own peculiar customs and ______of acting.  ",options:["attitudes","behavior","ways","means"],answer:"C"},{question:"China is _______the Great Wall. ",options:["on","famous","famous for","famous as"],answer:"C"},{question:"The dog was tearing the cloth ______its teeth.",options:["with","by","through","in"],answer:"A"},{question:"A man should not be judged always ______what he says.    ",options:["by","in","with","to"],answer:"A"},{question:"We will have a ________holiday after the exam. ",options:["two month","two-month","two month's","two-months"],answer:"B"},{question:"Mr Wang is going to teach you maths ______one year.",options:["with","on","for","to"],answer:"C"},{question:"The population of the earth ______increasing fast.               ",options:["is","are","were","have been"],answer:"A"},{question:"Mike is _______than Jack.",options:["careful","carefully","less careful","more carefuler"],answer:"C"},{question:"There _______a basket ball match this afternoon.",options:["is going to be","is going to have","is going to is","is going to has"],answer:"A"},{question:"Nobody _________to smoke in the cinema.",options:["allow","allows","is allowed","are allowed"],answer:"C"},{question:"______delicious these moon cake are!",options:["How a","What a","How","What"],answer:"C"},{question:"There's no food in the fridge. They _______shopping.",options:["go","are go","are going","are going to go"],answer:"C"},{question:"The soup smells ____. Would you like some?",options:["good","well","properly","finely"],answer:"A"},{question:"Picking apples was hard work, ________ they really enjoyed it.    ",options:["and","so","but","or"],answer:"C"},{question:'They have planted _______trees in SaiBei, It\'s a "Great Green Wall" of trees.',options:["million","millions","several","millions of"],answer:"D"},{question:"________ fine weather it is today!                 ",options:["What","How","What a","How a"],answer:"A"},{question:"1 haven't got a single ________ from Jane since last year.",options:["advice","news","message","information"],answer:"C"},{question:"The weather in Harbin is quite different from ________ in Hainan.   ",options:["that","it","the one","one"],answer:"A"},{question:"The headmaster came to the classroom and asked ________ what had happened.",options:["his students to tell him","being told","telling him","to tell"],answer:"A"},{question:"- Who's speaking? \n- This is Tom ________.",options:["speaks","spoken","speaking","saying"],answer:"C"},{question:"- I'm sorry. I am late due to the heavy traffic. \n- ________",options:["Well, it's OK.","No, it's all right.","You are welcome.","You are wrong."],answer:"A"},{question:"- Paul, _______? \n- Oh, that's my father!And beside him, my mother.",options:["what is the person over there","who's talking over there","what are they doing","which is that"],answer:"B"},{question:"- Could I borrow your car for a few days?\n- ________  ",options:["Yes, you may borrow.","Yes, go on.","Sure, here is the key. Enjoy your journey.","It doesn't matter."],answer:"C"},{question:"- Excuse me, how much is the jacket? \n- It's 499 Yuan. ________",options:["Oh, no. That's OK!","How do you like it?","Which do you prefer?","Would you like to try it on?"],answer:"D"},{question:"- Could you help me with my physics, please？\n- ________ ",options:["No, no way.","No, I couldn't.","No, I can't.","Sorry I can't. I have to go to a meeting right now."],answer:"D"},{question:"- Could I speak to Don Watkins, please？\n- ________ ",options:["Speaking, please.","Oh, how are you？","I'm listening.","I'm Don."],answer:"A"},{question:"- Thank you for inviting me.\n- _______ ",options:["I really had a happy time.","Oh, it's too late.","Thank you for coming.","Oh, so slowly?"],answer:"C"},{question:"- How was your trip to London, Jane?          \n- ___________ ",options:["Oh, wonderful indeed.","I went there alone.","The guide showed me the way.","By plane and by bus."],answer:"A"},{question:"- Congratulations! You won the first prize in today's speech contest.\n- ________ ",options:["Yes, I beat the others.","No, no, I didn't do it well.","Thank you.","It's a pleasure."],answer:"C"},{question:"- Please help yourself to the seafood.\n- ________ ",options:["No, I can't.","Sorry, I can't help.","Well, seafood don't suit.","Well, I'm afraid I don't like seafood."],answer:"D"},{question:"- Would you like to go to the concert with us this evening?\n- ________ ",options:["No, I already have plans.","I'd love to, but I'm busy tonight.","No, I really don't like being with you.","I'm ill, so I shouldn't go out."],answer:"B"},{question:"- Did you know that David injured his leg yesterday? \n- Really? _______ ",options:["Who did that?","What's wrong with him?","How did that happen?","Why was he so careless?"],answer:"C"},{question:"- This box is too heavy for me to carry it upstairs.\n- _______ ",options:["You may ask for help.","I'll give you a hand.","Please do me a favor.","I'd come to help."],answer:"B"},{question:"- Hey, Tom, what's up?\n- __________ ",options:["Yes, definitely!","Oh, not much.","What is happening in your life?","You are lucky."],answer:"B"},{question:"- Good morning, John. How are you doing?\n- _________ ",options:["I'm pleased.","Good night.","Not so bad. And you?","How do you do?"],answer:"C"},{question:"- Do you mind my smoking here?\n- _______ ",options:["No, thanks.","Yes, I do.","Yes. I'd rather not.","Good idea."],answer:"B"},{question:"- Excuse me, could you show me the way to the nearest post office? \n- ______Oh yes! Two blocks away from here at the Green Avenue. You can't miss it. ",options:["I beg your pardon?","What do you mean?","You're welcome.","Mm, let me think."],answer:"D"},{question:"- Wow! This is a marvelous room! I've never known you're so artistic.\n- ______ ",options:["Great, I am very art-conscious.","Don't mention it.","Thanks for your compliments.","It's fine."],answer:"C"},{question:"- I didn't mean to do that. Please forgive me.   \n- _________ ",options:["Not too bad.","That's all right.","It's a pleasure.","Thank you."],answer:"B"},{question:"- I wonder if I could use your computer tonight?          \n- ___________ I'm not using it right now. ",options:["Sure, here you are.","I don't know.","It doesn't matter.","Who cares?"],answer:"A"},{question:"- What do you think of this novel?\n- _________ ",options:["I've read it.","It's well-written.","It was written by my uncle.","I bought it yesterday."],answer:"B"},{question:"- Hello, how are you? \n- _________ ",options:["Hello, how are you?","How do you do?","Fine, thank you.","That's OK."],answer:"C"},{question:"- Thank you ever so much for your lovely gift.\n- _________ ",options:["Never mind","I'm glad you like it.","Please don't say so.","No, It's not so good."],answer:"B"},{question:"- How are you getting on today?\n- _________ ",options:["Very well.","How do you do?","I'm a doctor.","Nice to have known you."],answer:"A"},{question:"- Are you going on holiday for a long time?\n- _________ ",options:["It was a long time.","Two weeks ago.","No. Only a couple of days.","Not long time ago."],answer:"C"},{question:"- How tall is your sister?\n- _________ ",options:["She is not very well.","She is 28 years old.","She is very nice.","She is as tall as I am."],answer:"D"},{question:"- How can I get to the cinema?\n- _________ ",options:["It's very far.","Yes, there is a cinema near here.","It's well known.","Go down this street and turn left."],answer:"D"},{question:"- Good morning, may I speak to Mark, please?\n- _________ ",options:["Who's there?","Who's that speaking?","Who are you?","Who wants to speak to Mark?"],answer:"B"},{question:"- What's the matter, John?\n- _________ ",options:["I failed my French test.","It doesn't matter.","Nothing's wrong with him.","I don't think I can."],answer:"A"},{question:"- I'd like to invite you to dinner this Saturday, Mr. Smith.\n- _________",options:["Oh, no. let's not.","I'd rather stay at home.","I'm sorry, but I have other plans.","Oh, no. That'll be too much trouble."],answer:"C"},{question:"- Could you please open the window?\n- _________",options:["I can't.      ","Go ahead.    ","Sure.   ","It's really very kind."],answer:"C"},{question:"- Do you think I can borrow your bike for a few hours?\n- _________",options:["I'm afraid you can.          ","I'm sorry, but I really need it this afternoon.","Yes, I don't think so.           ","I'll think about it later."],answer:"B"},{question:"- Thank you very much for the dictionary you sent me.\n- _________",options:["No thanks.   ","I'm glad you like it. ","Please don't say so. ","No, it's not so good."],answer:"B"},{question:"- How do you like the movie we saw yesterday?\n- _________",options:["You are welcome.                              ","How about you?","I've never seen a better movie than it.      ","It is very expensive."],answer:"C"},{question:"- What do you think of your new teacher?\n- _________",options:["He came to teach us last week.","He teaches us English.","He has two children.","He is very nice."],answer:"D"},{question:"- Are you going to have a holiday?\n- _________",options:["Not until next week.","Three weeks ago.","To Beijing.","I'm pleased to hear that."],answer:"A"},{question:"- You seem to be lost. Need help?\t\n- _________",options:["Yes, would you please help me with the bag?\t\t","Help me find my key, please.","Yes, with pleasure.\t\t\t\t","I'm looking for Zhongshan Road. "],answer:"D"},{question:"- Can you help me clear up the mess?\n- _________",options:["Yes, it doesn't matter.","No, that's OK.","Yes, help yourself.","No problem."],answer:"D"},{question:"- Does No.20 bus stop at our school?\n- _________",options:["I go to school by bus.","I'm afraid not.","You are welcome.","I'll not take No.20 bus."],answer:"B"},{question:"- I think the reference book（参考书）is very helpful.\n- _________",options:["Good idea.\t\t\t\t\t\t","So do I.","With pleasure.","No problem."],answer:"B"},{question:"- Can I help you?\n- _________",options:["Sorry, I don't need your help.\t\t\t","What help can you give us?","I'd like to try on these shoes, please.","Thanks. You are welcome.\t "],answer:"C"},{question:"- Thanks for inviting me, John, but I've already made other plans. \n- _________. Maybe another time.",options:["I hope you enjoy it\t\t\t\t\t\t\t","That's good","Oh! I'm sorry to hear that          ","Great! I really had a good time"],answer:"C"},{question:"- How long have you worked here?\n- _________",options:["Since about two years.","I do not know.","For about two years.","Who knows."],answer:"C"},{question:"- Sorry to have kept you waiting. \n- _________",options:["That's OK.\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t","What are you doing?","What's wrong with you?\t\t\t\t\t\t","Where have you been?"],answer:"A"},{question:"- We are planning an outing. _________ \n- Sure.",options:["Where are you going?\t\t","When will you leave?\t\t","How is everything?\t","Do you want to join us?"],answer:"D"},{question:"- What is she?\n- _________",options:["She is a typist.","She is talking to her friend.","She is having a holiday.","She is my sister."],answer:"A"},{question:"- That's a beautiful cat. I wonder who it belongs to.\n- _________",options:["It belongs to the Browns.","The cat is my favourite too.","Mind your own business.","I can't say anything more."],answer:"A"},{question:"- Excuse me, could you tell me the time?\n- _________",options:["You'd better buy a watch.\t","It's three thirty by my watch.","Can you see the clock?\t\t\t","It's late I think."],answer:"B"},{question:"- What do you think of the movie we saw last night?\n- _________",options:["The actress is bad.","Terrific!","The theatre is bad. ","Nobody was there."],answer:"B"},{question:"－_______ \n－No, thanks. I'm just looking around. I'll let you know if I want anything.",options:["Could you help me?","What will you buy? ","Can I help you?","Do you like to look around? "],answer:"C"},{question:"- Hello, Peter. What do you do?\n- _________",options:["I am fine.","I am not sick.","I am a student from Bonn University.","I came from Bonn University."],answer:"C"},{question:"-Excuse me; can I have a seat here?\n- _______",options:["Be hurry.              \t\t\t","Come on.","Yes, please.          \t\t\t","Do you mind?"],answer:"C"},{question:"- Shall we sit up here on the grass or down there near the water?\n- _____",options:["I'd rather stay here if you don't mind.","Sorry, I don't like neither.","Certainly, why not？","Yes, we like these two places."],answer:"A"},{question:"- What do you do on Sunday?\n- _______",options:["I 'm a teacher.     ","I play football.    ","You are a student.   ","They clean rooms.  "],answer:"B"},{question:"- Our class won the girls' relay race in our school's sports meeting.\n- _____________________",options:["That's right.","Thanks a lot.","Congratulations!","It's a pleasure."],answer:"C"},{question:"- Hi, is Mary there, please?\n- _____",options:["Hold on. I'll get her.","No, she isn't here.","Yes, she lives here.","Yes, what do you want?"],answer:"A"},{question:"- I am afraid I can't return the book to you before Friday. \n-______. ",options:["Don't be afraid","Be careful","Not at all","Take your time"],answer:"D"},{question:"- I really don't know how to thank you enough.\n- ______.",options:["No problem","Think nothing of it","Not at all","It doesn't matter"],answer:"B"},{question:"- Must I be home before seven? \n- ___________________.",options:["No, you needn't","No, you mustn't","Yes, you will","No, you won't"],answer:"A"},{question:"-I'm sorry to hear that you failed in the exam.    \n-___________.",options:["Not at all","Oh, thank you.That's very kind of you","You are welcome","Yes, I'm really sorry"],answer:"B"},{question:"-If you need me, jut let me know.\n-I will,___________.",options:["that's all right","thank you","all right","not at all"],answer:"B"},{question:"-Hello, may I speak to Zhao Hua?\n-__________.",options:["My name is Zhao Hua","I'm Zhao Hua","This is Zhao Hua speaking","Zhao Hua is me"],answer:"C"},{question:"- _________? \n- This is Mr Smith speaking now.",options:["Who are you","Who is that","Who are you calling","What do you want to say"],answer:"B"},{question:"- I was born in Boston, but I studied in New York._________?\n- I was born in New York, but studied in Boston.",options:["What do you do","And you","Where were you","Do you"],answer:"B"},{question:"- I was worried about my maths, but Mr. Brown gave me an A.\n- _____",options:["Don't worry about it.","Congratulations! That's a difficult course.","Mr. Brown is very good.","Good luck to you！"],answer:"B"},{question:"-Would you go to the concert with me?\n-_____________, but I'm very busy now.",options:["I'd like to","Sure","No problem","Certainly"],answer:"A"},{question:"-Can I get you a cup of tea?      \n-___________.",options:["That's very kind of you","With pleasure","You can, please","Thank you for the tea"],answer:"A"},{question:"-I'll be away on a business trip. Would you mind looking at my cat?\n-Not at all. ____________.",options:["I have no time","I'd rather not","You can leave","I'd be happy to"],answer:"D"},{question:"- Hi, Jim! Nice to meet you.\n- _________.",options:["Certainly","Many thanks","OK","Nice to meet you, too"],answer:"D"},{question:"- Will you please give the note to him?\n- ______________.",options:["Certainly, I'll give it to him","No, please not","Sorry, I don't","Yes, please do"],answer:"A"},{question:"- Hello, may I speak to Mike?\n- __________",options:["Who are you?","Sorry, he isn't in.","Thank you very much.","Yes, here you are."],answer:"B"},{question:"- Will you join us for lunch?\n- _________.  ",options:["No, I won't","Yes, with pleasure","Yes, please","Yes, help yourself"],answer:"B"},{question:"- Thank you for your great dinner. I really enjoyed it.\n- __________you enjoyed it. ",options:["I'm so glad","I'm sorry","What a pity","Surprisingly"],answer:"A"},{question:"- I heard Susan surprised her teacher by working hard.    \n- Yes, ______",options:["her teacher worked hard.","Susan worked hard.","the teacher was surprising.","Susan was surprised."],answer:"B"},{question:"- Peter, don't step on the grass.\n-  ____________.",options:["It doesn't matter","I can't do it","Don't worry","Sorry, I won't do it again"],answer:"D"},{question:"- How was your journey to Paris? - _________",options:["It went very well.","I flew there.","I love Paris.","Thank you for asking."],answer:"A"},{question:"- I'm sorry for being late, Mr Lt.\n- ___________.",options:["All right","That's right","Not at all","Never mind"],answer:"D"},{question:"- Happy birthday to you!    \n- ______!",options:["Happy birthday to you","I'm very glad","That's all right","Thank you"],answer:"D"},{question:"- Do you like country music?\n-______________.",options:["Yes, I like basketball a lot","It's far too crowded","Yes, I'm crazy about it","Oh, it's funny"],answer:"C"},{question:"- Have a cup of tea, _________?     \n- Thanks a lot.",options:["don't you","haven't you","shall we","will you"],answer:"D"},{question:"- Thank God．It's Friday again．A nice weekend!\n- ______.",options:["Me too","Yes，I'll be free then","That's all right","The same to you"],answer:"D"},{question:"- I'll sorry to trouble you.\n- ___________.",options:["Don't say so","OK","It doesn't matter","That's fight"],answer:"C"},{question:"- We ordered 20 boxes of your products, but we have only got 19. - _________",options:["You do not have to.","It does not matter.","We will send another tomorrow.","Nothing serious."],answer:"C"},{question:"- How is it that you are late for class again?\n- ________________.",options:["Because I missed the bus","By bus and then on foot","Yes, it is quite wrong","It is far from school"],answer:"A"},{question:"- Excuse me. Could you spare me a few minutes? - _________",options:["Of course.","Of course not.","I am sorry to hear that.","Yes. I'm busy now."],answer:"A"},{question:"- How do I transfer calls? - _________",options:["Do as you like.","It is a bit difficult.","Let me show you.","Not at all."],answer:"C"},{question:"- It's very thoughtful of you to give me a ride. - _________",options:["It's my pleasure.","Take it easy.","Sure.","Never mind."],answer:"A"}]},e7a4:function(e,t,o){}});
//# sourceMappingURL=app.736aa17f.js.map